Adventist B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Health I-ORG
Sciences I-ORG

He O
was O
educated O
at O
Eton B-ORG
College I-ORG
and O
New B-ORG
College I-ORG
, I-ORG
Oxford I-ORG
. O

Chemung B-ORG
Speedrome I-ORG
- O
Chemung B-LOC
, O
New B-LOC
York I-LOC

: O
Headquarters O
, O
Thirteenth B-ORG
Air I-ORG
Force I-ORG
, O
13–21 O
January O
1943 O

1283 O
: O
The O
Yuan B-ORG
Dynasty I-ORG
claim O
possession O
of O
the O
Penghu B-ORG
Islands I-ORG

Proposition B-ORG
8 I-ORG
was O
validly O
adopted O
, O
and O
marriages O
contracted O
before O
its O
adoption O
remain O
valid O
. O

New B-ORG
York I-ORG
State I-ORG
Route I-ORG
5 I-ORG

IEEE B-ORG
Intelligent I-ORG
Transportation I-ORG
Systems I-ORG
Society I-ORG

' O
'' O
Jill B-PER
Hetherington I-PER
'' O
' O

1660 O
Sir B-PER
Matthew I-PER
Hale I-PER

F. B-PER
S. I-PER
L. I-PER
Lyons I-PER

Chris B-PER
Paul I-PER
( O
21 O
) O

Nicholas B-PER
G. I-PER
Carr I-PER

James B-PER
J. I-PER
Crawford I-PER
( O
1871– O
? O

' O
'' O
Maverick B-PER
Viñales I-PER
'' O
' O

Katie B-PER
Boyle I-PER
, O
born O
in O
Florence B-LOC
, O
Italy B-LOC
, O
by O
Italian B-LOC
/ O
Russian B-LOC
father O
and O
British B-LOC
/ O
Australian B-LOC
mother O
. O

It O
is O
found O
in O
Great B-LOC
Britain I-LOC
, O
Belgium B-LOC
, O
France B-LOC
, O
Portugal B-LOC
, O
Spain B-LOC
, O
Switzerland B-LOC
, O
Italy B-LOC
, O
Serbia B-ORG
and I-ORG
Montenegro I-ORG
and O
Bulgaria B-LOC
. O

It O
belongs O
to O
the O
Municipality B-LOC
of I-LOC
Sevnica I-LOC
. O

Dol B-LOC
, I-LOC
Stari I-LOC
Grad I-LOC

Heem B-PER
, I-PER
David I-PER
Cornelisz I-PER
de I-PER
( O
Antwerp B-LOC
1663 O
– O
The B-LOC
Hague I-LOC
? O

'' O
Metarctia B-LOC
atrivenata I-LOC
'' O
Kiriakoff O
, O
1956 O

' O
'' O
Bhutan B-LOC
'' O
' O

It O
is O
found O
on O
the O
Canary B-LOC
Islands I-LOC
and O
in O
North B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
, O
Turkey B-LOC
, O
Corsica B-LOC
, O
Sardinia B-LOC
, O
Cyprus B-LOC
, O
France B-LOC
, O
Croatia B-LOC
, O
Italy B-LOC
, O
Bulgaria B-LOC
, O
Greece B-LOC
and O
Portugal B-LOC
. O

