Železničná B-ORG
spoločnosť I-ORG
Slovensko I-ORG

The O
67 O
's O
finished O
in O
last O
place O
in O
the O
2012–13 B-ORG
OHL I-ORG
season I-ORG
with O
just O
16 O
wins O
. O

Internet B-ORG
Exchange I-ORG
Point I-ORG
( O
IXP O
) O

It O
was O
released O
as O
the O
first O
single O
from O
their O
2004 O
album O
Everybody B-ORG
Loves I-ORG
a I-ORG
Happy I-ORG
Ending I-ORG
'' O
and O
is O
the O
first O
single O
that O
features O
both O
original O
members O
Roland B-PER
Orzabal I-PER
and O
Curt B-PER
Smith I-PER
since O
1990 O
. O

'' O
Invisible B-ORG
Touch I-ORG
'' O
– O
Genesis B-ORG

Live B-ORG
at I-ORG
Sin-é I-ORG
( I-ORG
Legacy I-ORG
Edition I-ORG
) I-ORG
'' O

Aigle B-ORG
Noir I-ORG
AC I-ORG

Charlie B-PER
Clouser I-PER
– O
Nine B-ORG
Inch I-ORG
Nails I-ORG

Former B-ORG
collegiate I-ORG
church I-ORG
St I-ORG
Bartholomew I-ORG
, O
Liège B-LOC

Clement B-ORG
Poitrenaud I-ORG
, O
14 O
. O

1982 B-ORG
Tour I-ORG
de I-ORG
France I-ORG

'' O
Super B-ORG
World I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sports I-ORG
'' O
' O

Legend B-ORG
of I-ORG
Chun I-ORG
Hyang I-ORG
'' O

BBC B-ORG
( O
Test B-ORG
Match I-ORG
Special I-ORG
'' O
) O

It O
was O
also O
released O
along O
with O
Visual B-ORG
Studio I-ORG
2005 I-ORG
, O
Microsoft B-ORG
SQL I-ORG
Server I-ORG
2005 I-ORG
, O
and O
BizTalk B-ORG
2006 O
. O

** O
Kyoto B-ORG
National I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
( O
early O
production O
cast O
) O

List B-ORG
of I-ORG
years I-ORG
in I-ORG
Brazil I-ORG

Misawa B-ORG
AB I-ORG
, O
Japan B-LOC
, O
29 O
November O
1965 O
– O
15 O
May O
1971 O

16th B-ORG
Troop I-ORG
Carrier I-ORG
Squadron I-ORG
: O
attached O
14 O
November O
1954 O
– O
8 O
July O
1955 O

It O
sold O
184,000 O
in O
traditional O
album O
sales O
( O
down O
65 O
percent O
) O
and O
was O
beaten O
to O
the O
top O
by O
Adele B-PER
's O
25 B-ORG
'' O
, O
which O
debuted O
at O
number O
one O
with O
a O
record-breaking O
3.38 O
million O
. O

Super B-ORG
League I-ORG
Greece I-ORG
: O
1982–83 B-ORG

Guy B-PER
Berryman I-PER
( O
Coldplay B-ORG
) O

He O
is O
a O
former O
England B-ORG
under-21 I-ORG
international I-ORG
. O

Human B-ORG
Rights I-ORG
Commission I-ORG
of I-ORG
Malaysia I-ORG

The O
elevation O
is O
3944 O
feet O
( O
1202 O
m O
) O
above B-ORG
sea I-ORG
level I-ORG
. O

'' O
Space B-ORG
Heater I-ORG
( I-ORG
album I-ORG
) I-ORG
'' O

Thompson B-ORG
International I-ORG
Speedway I-ORG
– O
Thompson B-LOC
, I-LOC
Connecticut I-LOC

Recorded O
at O
Alberts B-ORG
Studio I-ORG
, O
London B-LOC
. O

**London O
: O
Thames B-ORG
& I-ORG
Hudson I-ORG
. O

Takht B-ORG
Sri I-ORG
Hazur I-ORG
Sahib I-ORG
, O
Nanded B-LOC

lifebelt]]s O
that O
survived O
the O
sinking O
is O
on O
display O
at O
the O
Imperial B-ORG
War I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
North I-ORG
in O
Manchester B-LOC

Borg B-ORG
El I-ORG
Arab I-ORG
Stadium I-ORG
, O
Alexandria B-LOC
, O
Egypt B-LOC

`` O
A B-ORG
Different I-ORG
Corner I-ORG
'' O

1283 O
: O
The O
Yuan B-ORG
Dynasty I-ORG
claim O
possession O
of O
the O
Penghu B-ORG
Islands I-ORG

**Monarch O
- O
George B-PER
V I-PER
, O
King B-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
United I-ORG
Kingdom I-ORG
( O
1910–1936 O
) O

New B-ORG
York I-ORG
State I-ORG
Route I-ORG
5 I-ORG

Des B-ORG
pères I-ORG
, I-ORG
des I-ORG
hommes I-ORG
et I-ORG
des I-ORG
frères I-ORG

Two B-ORG
and I-ORG
a I-ORG
Half I-ORG
Men I-ORG

5000-meter B-ORG
run I-ORG
– O
14:15.61 O
( O
2015 O
) O

Communist B-ORG
Party I-ORG
of I-ORG
Nigeria I-ORG
( O
CPN O
) O

** O
'' O
Chaetodon B-ORG
falcula I-ORG
'' O
, O
Blackwedged B-LOC
butterflyfish I-LOC

The O
first O
settlers O
arrived O
in O
the O
early O
19th O
century O
, O
and O
were O
largely O
Quakers B-ORG
, O
Mennonites B-ORG
and O
United B-ORG
Empire I-ORG
Loyalists I-ORG
who O
had O
left O
the O
United B-LOC
States I-LOC
. O

Estadio B-ORG
Tiburcio I-ORG
Carías I-ORG
Andino I-ORG
Tegucigalpa B-LOC
, O
Honduras B-LOC

St B-ORG
George I-ORG
's I-ORG
, I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
London I-ORG
( O
SGUL O
) O

Wales B-ORG
national I-ORG
football I-ORG
team I-ORG

*wisent O
( O
Bison B-ORG
bonasus I-ORG
'' O
) O

UEFA B-ORG
Cup I-ORG
winner O
1981 B-ORG
. O

Her O
grandson O
Stanley B-PER
Eric I-PER
Francis I-PER
Booth-Clibborn I-PER
became O
the O
Anglican B-ORG
Bishop B-LOC
of I-LOC
Manchester I-LOC
. O

It O
will O
serve O
the O
suburb O
of O
Murrumba B-ORG
Downs I-ORG
in O
the O
Moreton B-LOC
Bay I-LOC
Region I-LOC
. O

The B-ORG
Larry I-ORG
Sanders I-ORG
Show I-ORG
'' O

Coming O
on O
twice O
as O
a O
substitute O
, O
he O
was O
selected O
to O
start O
in O
the O
semi-final O
loss O
to O
Brazil B-ORG
. O

K. B-ORG
S. I-ORG
Rangasamy I-ORG
College I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG

St. B-ORG
Mary I-ORG
's I-ORG
College I-ORG
, I-ORG
Kegalle I-ORG

Classic B-ORG
Gold I-ORG
Marcher I-ORG
, O
Wrexham B-LOC
and O
Chester B-LOC

DRS B-ORG
1 I-ORG
- O
101.5 O
MHz O
( O
60 O
kW O
) O

Marvin B-PER
Dunnette I-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Minnesota I-ORG

Get B-ORG
off I-ORG
the I-ORG
Stage I-ORG

'' O
Şımarık B-ORG
'' O
– O
Tarkan B-PER

GMA B-ORG
Network I-ORG
was O
also O
reportedly O
planning O
to O
bid O
but O
backed O
out O
; O
it O
however O
denied O
that O
they O
offered O
a O
bid O
. O

K. B-ORG
Stade I-ORG
Leuven I-ORG
( O
1903—2002 O
) O

Image O
: O
V02p108001 O
Esnoga B-ORG
, O
Amsterdam B-LOC
, O
Netherlands B-LOC

Circuit B-ORG
rider I-ORG
( I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) I-ORG

He O
was O
the O
manager O
of O
Árabe B-ORG
Unido I-ORG
in O
Panama B-LOC
. O

*20px O
Indiana B-ORG
State I-ORG
Road I-ORG
18 I-ORG

Winnie B-ORG
the I-ORG
Pooh I-ORG
( I-ORG
franchise I-ORG
) I-ORG

The O
eastward O
pressure O
to O
expand O
was O
also O
created O
by O
the O
inability O
to O
move O
westward O
, O
inhibited O
by O
the O
formidable O
presence O
of O
the O
enormous O
Flushing B-LOC
Chinatown I-LOC
( I-LOC
法拉盛華埠 I-LOC
) I-LOC
centered O
on O
Main B-ORG
Street I-ORG
. O

List B-ORG
of I-ORG
national I-ORG
libraries I-ORG

`` O
Who B-ORG
Loves I-ORG
You I-ORG
? I-ORG
'' O

** O
Southern B-ORG
Maryland I-ORG
Blue I-ORG
Crabs I-ORG

List B-ORG
of I-ORG
famous I-ORG
Puerto I-ORG
Ricans I-ORG

William B-ORG
Morrow I-ORG
and I-ORG
Company I-ORG

In O
1841 O
the O
population O
of O
Norbury B-ORG
and I-ORG
Roston I-ORG
was O
510 O
, O
in O
1895 O
there O
were O
414 O
inhabitants O
. O

AFL]] O
( O
Australian B-ORG
rules I-ORG
) O

Bahawalpur B-ORG
Zoo I-ORG
, O
Bahawalpur B-LOC
, O
Punjab B-ORG

List B-ORG
of I-ORG
Orchidaceae I-ORG
genera I-ORG

Clarkston B-ORG
railway I-ORG
station I-ORG

Rimyongsu B-ORG
Sports I-ORG
Club I-ORG
( O
Sariwon B-LOC
) O

1944 O
Presentation B-ORG
Brothers I-ORG
College I-ORG

''Also O
see O
: O
Hot B-ORG
100 I-ORG
No. I-ORG
1 I-ORG
Hits I-ORG
of I-ORG
1979 I-ORG
'' O

Masonic B-ORG
Temple I-ORG
Building I-ORG
( I-ORG
Maywood I-ORG
, I-ORG
Illinois I-ORG
) I-ORG

Shake B-ORG
( I-ORG
company I-ORG
) I-ORG

He O
ultimately O
returned O
to O
the O
Boston B-ORG
Globe I-ORG
'' O
, O
where O
he O
had O
been O
working O
immediately O
before O
the O
''Tribune O
'' O
had O
hired O
him O
. O

United B-ORG
States I-ORG
Department I-ORG
of I-ORG
Labor I-ORG

The O
first O
3 O
songs O
as O
PopCrush O
97.1 O
were O
Pitbull B-PER
/ O
Christina B-PER
Aguilera I-PER
's O
Feel B-ORG
This I-ORG
Moment I-ORG
'' O
, O
Justin B-PER
Timberlake I-PER
's O
Mirrors B-ORG
'' O
, O
and O
Rihanna B-PER
's O
Umbrella B-ORG
'' O
. O

** O
' O
'' O
Nanhai B-ORG
'' O
' O
– O
Liu B-PER
Yin I-PER
, O
King B-ORG
of I-ORG
Nanhai I-ORG
( O
907–911 O
) O

Siege B-ORG
of I-ORG
Naples I-ORG
( I-ORG
542–43 I-ORG
) I-ORG

Clarence B-PER
Tommerson I-PER
, O
NFL B-ORG
player O

' O
'' O
Angiosperms B-ORG
'' O
' O

List B-ORG
of I-ORG
Indonesian I-ORG
birds I-ORG
: I-ORG
non-passerines I-ORG

The O
song O
is O
included O
in O
the O
album O
Yanni B-ORG
Voces I-ORG
'' O
. O

WTUA B-ORG
St. B-LOC
Stephen I-LOC
, I-LOC
South I-LOC
Carolina I-LOC

Taebong B-ORG
has O
been O
overthrown O
, O
and O
Goryeo B-ORG
established O
in O
the O
Korean B-ORG
peninsula I-ORG
, O
when O
Wang B-ORG
Kon I-ORG
ascends O
the O
throne O
at O
Cheorwon B-LOC
. O

Flick B-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Switch I-ORG
'' O

1911 O
Yeon B-ORG
Building I-ORG
, O
Portland B-LOC
, I-LOC
Oregon I-LOC

`` O
O B-ORG
Come I-ORG
All I-ORG
Ye I-ORG
Faithful I-ORG
'' O

Dick B-ORG
's I-ORG
Sporting I-ORG
Goods I-ORG
( O
80,000 O
ft² O
) O

'' O
CONCACAF B-ORG
Champions I-ORG
' I-ORG
Cup I-ORG
: O
' O
'' O

Myrtle B-ORG
Beach I-ORG
, O
United B-LOC
States I-LOC

How B-ORG
to I-ORG
Save I-ORG
a I-ORG
Life I-ORG
'' O

Parken B-ORG
, O
Copenhagen B-LOC
( O
H O
) O

Now O
under O
control O
of O
482nd B-ORG
Fighter I-ORG
Wing I-ORG
( O
Air B-ORG
Force I-ORG
Reserve I-ORG
Command I-ORG
) O
and O
Detachment O
1 O
, O
125th B-ORG
Fighter I-ORG
Wing I-ORG
( O
Florida B-ORG
Air I-ORG
National I-ORG
Guard I-ORG
) O

Chimneys O
of O
Poolbeg B-ORG
Generating I-ORG
Station I-ORG

This B-ORG
Hour I-ORG
Has I-ORG
22 I-ORG
Minutes I-ORG
'' O
cast O

Bernhard B-ORG
Warkentin I-ORG
Homestead I-ORG

Same O
applied O
to O
Polish B-ORG
Americans I-ORG
. O

Martin B-PER
Sheen I-PER
- O
The B-ORG
West I-ORG
Wing I-ORG
'' O

`` O
U B-ORG
Got I-ORG
It I-ORG
Bad I-ORG
'' O

Bright B-ORG
Size I-ORG
Life I-ORG
'' O
– O
Pat B-PER
Metheny I-PER

Aborigines B-ORG
' I-ORG
Protection I-ORG
Society I-ORG

Previously O
, O
he O
was O
head O
coach O
at O
Alcorn B-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
and O
an O
assistant O
coach O
at O
Tulane B-ORG
, O
Delta B-ORG
State I-ORG
, O
LSU B-ORG
, O
Florida B-ORG
, O
Marshall B-ORG
, O
Southern B-ORG
Miss I-ORG
, O
Ole B-ORG
Miss I-ORG
, O
Michigan B-ORG
, O
and O
Memphis B-LOC
. O

Oriole B-ORG
Park I-ORG
at I-ORG
Camden I-ORG
Yards I-ORG
in O
Baltimore B-ORG
, I-ORG
Maryland I-ORG
, O
United B-LOC
States I-LOC

Massachusetts B-ORG
Route I-ORG
3A I-ORG

File O
: O
Tiananmen B-ORG
( O
天安门 O
) O

Episode O
: O
`` O
It B-ORG
's I-ORG
My I-ORG
Party I-ORG
and I-ORG
I I-ORG
'll I-ORG
Lie I-ORG
if I-ORG
I I-ORG
Want I-ORG
To I-ORG
'' O

FM B-ORG
Radio I-ORG
Gods I-ORG

'' O
Aztec B-LOC
Empire I-LOC
'' O
' O
– O
Tenoch B-PER
, O
Great B-ORG
Speaker I-ORG
( O
1325–1376 O
) O

' O
'' O
Speed B-ORG
Up I-ORG
'' O
' O

He O
graduated O
in O
1970 O
with O
a O
Doctor B-ORG
of I-ORG
veterinary I-ORG
medicine I-ORG
degree O
from O
the O
Ontario B-ORG
Veterinary I-ORG
College I-ORG
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Guelph I-ORG
in O
nearby O
Guelph B-LOC
, O
Ontario B-LOC
. O

Peru B-LOC
: O
Peruvian B-ORG
Communist I-ORG
Party I-ORG

The B-ORG
Dirty I-ORG
Dozen I-ORG
Brass I-ORG
Band I-ORG

Marshal B-ORG
( I-ORG
Japan I-ORG
) I-ORG

St B-ORG
Ann I-ORG
's I-ORG
College I-ORG

`` O
I B-ORG
Promise I-ORG
to I-ORG
Wait I-ORG
My I-ORG
Love I-ORG
'' O

National B-ORG
Nursing I-ORG
Week I-ORG
( O
United B-LOC
States I-LOC
) O

The B-ORG
Outdoor I-ORG
Room I-ORG

Hell B-ORG
: I-ORG
The I-ORG
Sequel I-ORG
'' O

He O
was O
educated O
at O
the O
Community B-ORG
High I-ORG
School I-ORG
, I-ORG
Tehran I-ORG
and O
then O
Carlisle B-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
. O

In O
1960 O
, O
he O
joined O
the O
U.S. B-ORG
Army I-ORG
, O
being O
stationed O
in O
Germany B-LOC
for O
three O
years O
. O

Beijing B-ORG
No.8 I-ORG
High I-ORG
School I-ORG

''Review O
: O
Something O
Better O
to O
Come O
'' O
at O
Slant B-ORG
Magazine I-ORG

Returning O
to O
Norfolk B-LOC
, I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
, O
1 O
April O
1946 O
, O
''Calamares O
'' O
was O
decommissioned O
at O
Baltimore B-ORG
, I-ORG
Maryland I-ORG
, O
25 O
April O
1946 O
, O
and O
returned O
to O
the O
War B-ORG
Shipping I-ORG
Administration I-ORG
. O

Southampton B-ORG
F.C I-ORG
. I-ORG

The O
Churches B-ORG
Conservation I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
now O
cares O
for O
the O
building O
. O

Growing B-ORG
Up I-ORG
( I-ORG
The I-ORG
T.G.I.S. I-ORG
Primetime I-ORG
) I-ORG

Following O
its O
sale O
by O
the O
New B-ORG
Zealand I-ORG
Railways I-ORG
Corporation I-ORG
in O
the O
1990s O
, O
the O
building O
was O
turned O
into O
student O
accommodation O
by O
Auckland B-ORG
University I-ORG
and O
since O
2008 O
has O
been O
occupied O
by O
private O
apartments O
. O

53d B-ORG
Wing I-ORG
( O
53 O
WG O
) O

Oda B-ORG
Station I-ORG
( I-ORG
Shimane I-ORG
) I-ORG
( O
小田駅 O
) O

Tales B-ORG
from I-ORG
Turnpike I-ORG
House I-ORG
'' O

Aboudeïa B-ORG
– O
Salamat B-LOC
Region I-LOC

Live B-ORG
- O
`` O
Run B-ORG
to I-ORG
the I-ORG
Water I-ORG
'' O

He O
spent O
much O
of O
his O
career O
with O
Swindon B-ORG
Town I-ORG
, O
for O
whom O
he O
played O
in O
the O
Premier B-ORG
League I-ORG
. O

The O
Eastwood B-ORG
Westminster I-ORG
constituency I-ORG
was O
created O
in O
1983 O
, O
and O
the O
Eastwood B-ORG
Holyrood I-ORG
constituency I-ORG
, O
with O
the O
same O
boundaries O
, O
in O
1999 O
. O

67 O
competitors O
were O
selected O
by O
the O
DLV B-ORG
. O

Bobby B-ORG
's I-ORG
Burger I-ORG
Palace I-ORG

This O
was O
published O
by O
the O
American B-ORG
Mathematical I-ORG
Society I-ORG
as O
ISSN O
0038-5573 O
. O

''The B-ORG
Times I-ORG
'' I-ORG
( I-ORG
Chicago I-ORG
) I-ORG
, O
went O
defunct O
in O
2005 O

Ronaldinho B-ORG
Gaucho I-ORG
's I-ORG
Team I-ORG

Tennessee B-ORG
in I-ORG
the I-ORG
Civil I-ORG
War I-ORG

Minarete B-ORG
Brass I-ORG
'' O
( O
2010 O
) O

*2008 O
– O
`` O
All B-ORG
Summer I-ORG
Long I-ORG
'' O
– O
Kid B-PER
Rock I-PER

It B-ORG
's I-ORG
No I-ORG
Good I-ORG

DCLXVI B-ORG
: I-ORG
To I-ORG
Ride I-ORG
Shoot I-ORG
Straight I-ORG
and I-ORG
Speak I-ORG
the I-ORG
Truth I-ORG
'' O

McCoy B-ORG
'' O
( O
1975-1976 O
) O

The B-ORG
Price I-ORG
Is I-ORG
Right I-ORG
( I-ORG
Philippine I-ORG
game I-ORG
show I-ORG
) I-ORG
'' O

Royal B-ORG
Australian I-ORG
Corps I-ORG
of I-ORG
Transport I-ORG
- O
The B-ORG
Princess I-ORG
Royal I-ORG

Johor B-ORG
Bahru I-ORG
City I-ORG
Square I-ORG

Mount B-ORG
Marty I-ORG
College I-ORG
( O
Yankton B-LOC
, I-LOC
South I-LOC
Dakota I-LOC
) O

Three B-ORG
's I-ORG
a I-ORG
Crowd I-ORG

' O
'' O
Persiaran B-ORG
APEC I-ORG
'' O
' O

Harvard B-ORG
Business I-ORG
School I-ORG
Press I-ORG
( O
2013 O
) O
Managing O
Up O
: O
Expert O
Solutions O
to O
Everyday O
Challenges O

St. B-ORG
Mary I-ORG
's I-ORG
Church I-ORG
, I-ORG
South I-ORG
Stoneham I-ORG

Sun B-PER
Quan I-PER
: O
Nabatame B-ORG
Hitomi I-ORG

`` O
I B-ORG
'll I-ORG
Walk I-ORG
'' O

Silver B-ORG
Slipper I-ORG
, O
Las B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
, I-LOC
Nevada I-LOC

Top B-ORG
Chef I-ORG
: I-ORG
Just I-ORG
Desserts I-ORG
'' O

`` O
Wake B-ORG
Up I-ORG
Brother I-ORG
'' O

The O
' O
'' O
1994 O
Big B-ORG
Ten I-ORG
Conference I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
Tournament I-ORG
'' O
' O
was O
held O
at O
C. B-ORG
O. I-ORG
Brown I-ORG
Stadium I-ORG
in O
Battle B-LOC
Creek I-LOC
, I-LOC
Michigan I-LOC
from O
May O
15 O
through O
19 O
. O

`` O
Carnival B-ORG
'' O
– O
Natalie B-PER
Merchant I-PER

2000 O
- O
Servants B-ORG
of I-ORG
Darkness I-ORG
'' O

The O
demand O
is O
$ B-ORG
. O

The B-ORG
People I-ORG
's I-ORG
Petition I-ORG

He O
became O
a O
journalist O
for O
The B-ORG
Nashville I-ORG
American I-ORG
'' O
, O
serving O
as O
a O
correspondent O
from O
1885 O
to O
1892 O
. O

** O
Basilica B-ORG
of I-ORG
San I-ORG
Isidoro I-ORG
, O
León B-LOC
, I-LOC
Spain I-LOC
consecrated O
. O

' O
'' O
Venue O
: O
' O
'' O
Daegu B-ORG
Civic I-ORG
Stadium I-ORG
, O
Daegu B-LOC

Parliamentary B-ORG
elections I-ORG
on I-ORG
22 I-ORG
September I-ORG
2002 I-ORG
: O
44.1 O
% O
of O
the O
primary O
vote O

NALSAR B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Law I-ORG
, O
Hyderabad B-LOC

Toronto B-LOC
, O
Ontario B-LOC
- O
CITY B-ORG

`` O
Livin B-ORG
' I-ORG
on I-ORG
Borrowed I-ORG
Time I-ORG
'' O

Broadcaster O
RAI B-ORG
chose O
the O
song O
and O
performer O
internally O
. O

Mystery B-ORG
Science I-ORG
Theater I-ORG
3000 I-ORG
'' O

Byzantium B-ORG
under I-ORG
the I-ORG
Macedonians I-ORG

1 O
: O
`` O
No B-ORG
News I-ORG
'' O
, O
`` O
Come B-ORG
Cryin I-ORG
' I-ORG
to I-ORG
Me I-ORG
'' O
, O
`` O
Amazed B-ORG
'' O
, O
`` O
Smile B-ORG
'' O
, O
`` O
What B-ORG
About I-ORG
Now I-ORG
'' O
, O
`` O
Tell B-ORG
Her I-ORG
'' O
, O
`` O
I B-ORG
'm I-ORG
Already I-ORG
There I-ORG
'' O
, O
`` O
My B-ORG
Front I-ORG
Porch I-ORG
Looking I-ORG
In I-ORG
'' O
, O
and O
`` O
Mr. B-ORG
Mom I-ORG
'' O
. O

Shakira B-PER
– O
`` O
Ojos B-ORG
Así I-ORG
'' O

The B-ORG
Threshold I-ORG
of I-ORG
a I-ORG
Persona I-ORG

The O
John B-ORG
Tracy I-ORG
Clinic I-ORG
, O
named O
after O
her O
son O
, O
was O
the O
result O
. O

*The O
Bennington B-ORG
Battle I-ORG
Monument I-ORG
in O
Bennington B-LOC
, I-LOC
Vermont I-LOC
, O
1889 O
. O

Westwood B-ORG
College I-ORG
– O
Dallas B-ORG
, I-ORG
Texas I-ORG

Part O
of O
the O
state-owned O
Main B-ORG
Line I-ORG
of I-ORG
Public I-ORG
Works I-ORG

Alexandru B-PER
Popovici I-PER
( O
2001 O
Seongnam B-ORG
Ilhwa I-ORG
Chunma I-ORG
) O

' O
'' O
If B-ORG
You I-ORG
Ai I-ORG
n't I-ORG
Got I-ORG
a I-ORG
Weapon I-ORG
... I-ORG
'' O

It O
consists O
of O
the O
Bundesautobahn B-ORG
3 I-ORG
, O
the O
Bundesautobahn B-ORG
4 I-ORG
and O
the O
Bundesautobahn B-ORG
1 I-ORG
. O

There O
have O
been O
five O
winners O
to O
date O
: O
Leanne B-PER
Mitchell I-PER
, O
Andrea B-PER
Begley I-PER
, O
Jermain B-PER
Jackman I-PER
, O
Stevie B-ORG
McCrorie I-ORG
and O
Kevin B-PER
Simm I-PER
. O

' O
'' O
14 O
Porsche B-ORG
'' O
' O
'' O

He O
subsequently O
worked O
for O
ABC B-ORG
affiliate O
WUTR B-ORG
in O
Utica B-LOC
, I-LOC
New I-LOC
York I-LOC
, O
CBS B-ORG
affiliate O
WTVH B-ORG
in O
Syracuse B-LOC
, I-LOC
New I-LOC
York I-LOC
, O
and O
NBC B-ORG
affiliate O
WCNC-TV B-ORG
in O
Charlotte B-LOC
, I-LOC
North I-LOC
Carolina I-LOC
. O

2013 B-ORG
Africa I-ORG
Cup I-ORG
of I-ORG
Nations I-ORG
qualification I-ORG

'' O
' O
'' O
After B-ORG
the I-ORG
Love I-ORG
Has I-ORG
Gone I-ORG
'' O
Earth B-ORG
, I-ORG
Wind I-ORG
& I-ORG
Fire I-ORG
'' O
' O

Tazmania B-ORG
'' O
( O
2006 O
) O

' O
'' O
President B-ORG
's I-ORG
Cup I-ORG
'' O
' O

'' O
Tokimeki B-ORG
Memorial I-ORG
: I-ORG
Forever I-ORG
With I-ORG
You I-ORG
'' O

It O
premiered O
on O
27 O
June O
2010 O
on O
YouTube B-ORG
. O

In O
1854 O
he O
was O
appointed O
to O
a O
seat O
on O
the O
Legislative B-ORG
Council I-ORG
of I-ORG
Nova I-ORG
Scotia I-ORG
, O
upon O
the O
recommendation O
of O
William B-PER
Young I-PER
. O

Twickenham B-ORG
Stadium I-ORG
, O
London B-LOC
, O
England B-LOC

The O
song O
was O
recorded O
at O
Grouse B-ORG
Lodge I-ORG
, O
under O
the O
supervision O
of O
producer O
Jacknife B-PER
Lee I-PER
. O

San B-ORG
Pedro I-ORG
y I-ORG
San B-ORG
Pablo I-ORG
Asistencia I-ORG

Lyraka B-ORG
Volume I-ORG
1 I-ORG
( O
2010 O
) O
'' O

His O
death O
was O
profiled O
in O
an O
episode O
of O
Unsolved B-ORG
Mysteries I-ORG
'' O
. O

Highest O
total O
against O
: O
224 O
/ O
7 O
by O
Somerset B-ORG
at O
Taunton B-LOC
, O
2015 O

All B-ORG
Saints I-ORG
Cathedral I-ORG
, I-ORG
Halifax I-ORG

Beginning O
of O
Karoo B-ORG
Ice I-ORG
Age I-ORG
. O

It O
is O
housed O
in O
the O
Musée B-ORG
du I-ORG
Louvre I-ORG
of O
Paris B-LOC
. O

Lotte B-ORG
Jonathans I-ORG
Paulien B-PER
van I-PER
Dooremalen I-PER

Millonarios B-ORG
F.C I-ORG
. I-ORG

Pioneer B-ORG
Square I-ORG
, I-ORG
Seattle I-ORG

The O
family O
eventually O
settled O
in O
Egypt B-ORG
in O
February O
1944 O
. O

'' O
Pumped B-ORG
Up I-ORG
Kicks I-ORG
'' O
– O
Foster B-ORG
the I-ORG
People I-ORG

Brian B-ORG
Dillons I-ORG
GAA I-ORG

Slavko B-PER
Marić I-PER
– O
Hajduk B-ORG
Beograd I-ORG
( O
2001–2006 O
) O
, O
Mladost B-ORG
Lučani I-ORG
( O
2006–2008 O
) O
, O
Borac B-ORG
Čačak I-ORG
( O
2008–2011 O
) O
, O
Sloboda B-ORG
Užice I-ORG
( O
2011–2012 O
) O
, O
Radnički B-ORG
Kragujevac I-ORG
( O
2012-2014 O
) O
, O
' O
'' O
FK B-ORG
Jagodina I-ORG
'' O
' O
( O
2015–present O
) O

Redlich–Kwong B-ORG
equation I-ORG
of I-ORG
state I-ORG

Yu B-PER
Darvish I-PER
( O
TEX B-ORG
) O
: O

'' O
Samurai B-ORG
7 I-ORG
'' O

Party B-ORG
of I-ORG
Action I-ORG
( I-ORG
POA I-ORG
) I-ORG

Children B-ORG
's I-ORG
Day I-ORG
Festival I-ORG

Final B-ORG
Fantasy I-ORG
concerts I-ORG

' O
'' O
20px O
99 B-ORG
Villeray I-ORG
'' O
' O

A B-ORG
Few I-ORG
Days I-ORG
with I-ORG
Me I-ORG
'' O

R. B-PER
Kelly I-PER
– O
`` O
Satisfy B-ORG
You I-ORG
'' O

Turkish B-ORG
films I-ORG
of I-ORG
2010 I-ORG

Latter B-ORG
Day I-ORG
Church I-ORG
of I-ORG
Christ I-ORG

' O
'' O
DLCX O
'' O
' O
- O
Waste B-ORG
Management I-ORG
, I-ORG
Inc I-ORG
. I-ORG

the O
`` O
Twelve B-ORG
Steps I-ORG
'' O
at O
the O
beginning O
of O
Chapter O
5 O
`` O
How O
It O
Works O
'' O

'' O
Volumes B-ORG
3 I-ORG
& I-ORG
4 I-ORG
'' O
( O
1998 O
) O

Cauchy B-ORG
's I-ORG
theorem I-ORG
( I-ORG
geometry I-ORG
) I-ORG

Eaton B-ORG
High I-ORG
School I-ORG
( O
grades O
9-12 O
) O

C.D. B-ORG
Atlético I-ORG
Junior I-ORG

Stick B-ORG
( I-ORG
unit I-ORG
) I-ORG

Bridgwater B-ORG
Town I-ORG
, O
promoted O
as O
runners-up O
in O
Western B-LOC
League I-LOC

Exeter B-ORG
Cathedral I-ORG
1929 O
- O
1937 O

''Crockett O
'' O
was O
laid O
down O
by O
the O
Tacoma B-ORG
Boatbuilding I-ORG
Company I-ORG
, O
Tacoma B-LOC
, I-LOC
Washington I-LOC
, O
and O
commissioned O
24 O
June O
1967 O
. O

Football B-ORG
League I-ORG
Two I-ORG
third-place O
promotion O
: O
2005–06 B-ORG

International B-ORG
Swimming I-ORG
Federation I-ORG
( I-ORG
FINA I-ORG
) I-ORG

Air B-ORG
Command I-ORG
and I-ORG
Staff I-ORG
College I-ORG
, O
Seminar O
Program O

'' O
Eilema B-ORG
depressa I-ORG
'' O
( O
Esper O
, O
1787 O
) O

North B-ORG
Carolina I-ORG
General I-ORG
Assembly I-ORG
of I-ORG
2003–04 I-ORG

'' O
Robopit B-ORG
'' O
- O
Kokopeli B-ORG
Digital I-ORG
Studios I-ORG
/ O
Altron B-ORG

Vasil B-ORG
Levski I-ORG
National I-ORG
Military I-ORG
University I-ORG
, O
Veliko B-LOC
Tarnovo I-LOC

Member O
of O
Finnish B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sciences I-ORG
, O
2002– O

Michael B-PER
Jackson I-PER
– O
`` O
Earth B-ORG
Song I-ORG
'' O

National B-ORG
Union I-ORG
of I-ORG
Students I-ORG
( I-ORG
Canada I-ORG
) I-ORG
( O
disbanded O
) O

The O
resulting O
album O
, O
Last B-ORG
Fair I-ORG
Deal I-ORG
Gone I-ORG
Down I-ORG
'' O
was O
released O
in O
May O
2001 O
. O

Persona B-ORG
2 I-ORG
: I-ORG
Innocent I-ORG
Sin I-ORG

`` O
Express B-ORG
Yourself I-ORG
'' O
, O
Madonna B-PER
( O
1989 O
) O

Thalhimers B-ORG
( O
Richmond B-LOC
) O

He O
is O
part O
of O
the O
Czech B-ORG
Republic I-ORG
men I-ORG
's I-ORG
national I-ORG
volleyball I-ORG
team I-ORG
. O

800BC O
( O
in O
The B-ORG
Odyssey I-ORG
'' O
) O

' O
'' O
Turkish B-ORG
Super I-ORG
Cup I-ORG
'' O
' O
'' O

He O
joined O
Ayr B-ORG
United I-ORG
in O
August O
1999 O
, O
and O
remained O
with O
them O
until O
August O
2000 O
. O

' O
'' O
Perth B-ORG
Thunder I-ORG
'' O
' O

Maria B-ORG
Adams I-ORG
( I-ORG
disambiguation I-ORG
) I-ORG

Basilica B-ORG
della I-ORG
Santa I-ORG
Casa I-ORG

Full B-ORG
Circle I-ORG
'' O
( O
2004 O
) O

Barry B-ORG
Mackay I-ORG
'' O
( O
Quarterfinalist O
) O
'' O

Represented O
Indigenous B-ORG
All-Stars I-ORG
( O
2009 O
) O

Southend B-ORG
United I-ORG
F.C I-ORG
. I-ORG

Episodes B-ORG
'' O
, O
2011 O
( O
writer O
/ O
producer O
) O

1992 B-ORG
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
expansion I-ORG
draft I-ORG

Cark B-ORG
and I-ORG
Cartmel I-ORG
railway I-ORG
station I-ORG

National B-ORG
Coalition I-ORG
Party I-ORG
13.5 O
% O

Beauvoir B-PER
De I-PER
Lisle I-PER
, O
1st B-ORG
Dragoons I-ORG
, O
commanded O
both O
the O
XIII B-ORG
and O
XV B-ORG
Corps I-ORG
. O

`` B-ORG
Sign I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Times I-ORG
'' I-ORG
( I-ORG
Bryan I-ORG
Ferry I-ORG
song I-ORG
) I-ORG
, O
1978 O

Lake B-LOC
of I-LOC
Banyoles I-LOC
and O
S'Agaró B-ORG

Buxton B-ORG
& I-ORG
Leek I-ORG
College I-ORG

'' O
The B-ORG
World I-ORG
at I-ORG
Large I-ORG
'' O
– O
4:32 O

State B-ORG
Senate I-ORG
District I-ORG
39 I-ORG

Miyazaki B-ORG
Athletic I-ORG
Stadium I-ORG

: O
'' O
Atomic B-ORG
Dog I-ORG
'' O
by O
George B-PER
Clinton I-PER

C B-ORG
& I-ORG
D I-ORG
Canal I-ORG
Museum I-ORG

`` O
Stupid B-ORG
Shit I-ORG
'' O
– O
Girlicious B-ORG

Burmese–Siamese B-ORG
War I-ORG
( I-ORG
1759–60 I-ORG
) I-ORG

Dance4life B-ORG
event O
2006 O
. O

'' O
'Megahertz O
'' O
' O
from O
Mighty B-ORG
Med I-ORG
'' O

All O
degrees O
( O
whether O
traditional O
on-campus O
, O
or O
distance O
) O
are O
recognized O
by O
the O
New B-ORG
England I-ORG
Association I-ORG
of I-ORG
Schools I-ORG
and I-ORG
Colleges I-ORG
and O
the O
State B-ORG
of I-ORG
Connecticut I-ORG
; O
. O

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Massachusetts I-ORG
Boston I-ORG

The O
song O
contains O
samples O
from O
`` O
Try B-ORG
Again I-ORG
'' O
by O
Aaliyah B-PER
, O
`` O
Breathe B-ORG
and I-ORG
Stop I-ORG
'' O
by O
Q-Tip B-PER
, O
and O
`` O
N.T O
. O

Holy B-ORG
Trinity I-ORG
Church I-ORG
, I-ORG
Blythburgh I-ORG

'' O
Pick-Up B-ORG
'' O
( O
1933 O
) O
with O
Sylvia B-PER
Sidney I-PER

He O
was O
TV-host O
for O
Parlamentet B-ORG
in O
2011 O
. O

' O
'' O
7th B-ORG
US I-ORG
Army I-ORG
HQ I-ORG
, O
Heidelberg B-LOC
'' O
' O
, O
FRG O

Sivaji B-PER
Ganesan I-PER
, O
Sripriya B-PER
, O
V.K. B-ORG
Ramasamy I-ORG

Free B-ORG
Software I-ORG
Foundation I-ORG
Europe I-ORG

Way B-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Blade I-ORG
'' O
( O
2006 O
) O

NBA B-ORG
Rookie I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Year I-ORG
: O
2007 O

A O
modern O
Twist B-ORG
( I-ORG
ride I-ORG
) I-ORG
. O

The O
album O
was O
a O
commercial O
success O
and O
sold O
almost O
eight O
million O
copies O
, O
according O
to O
Billboard B-ORG
'' O
. O

Jaipur B-LOC
( O
Palace B-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Winds I-ORG
) O

US B-ORG
Amateur I-ORG
– O
Bobby B-PER
Jones I-PER

Port B-LOC
of I-LOC
Spain I-LOC
, O
Trinidad B-ORG
and I-ORG
Tobago I-ORG

' O
'' O
Women B-ORG
's I-ORG
10,000 I-ORG
metres I-ORG
'' O
' O

New B-ORG
Forest I-ORG
Wildlife I-ORG
Park I-ORG
- O
Hampshire B-LOC

`` O
California B-ORG
Gurls I-ORG
'' O
- O
Katy B-PER
Perry I-PER

19 O
, O
, O
Stockholm B-LOC
, O
Cirkus B-ORG

Waverly B-ORG
School I-ORG
District I-ORG
( I-ORG
disambiguation I-ORG
) I-ORG

2004 O
: O
Real B-ORG
Gone I-ORG
Tour I-ORG
'' O

Interstate B-ORG
88 I-ORG
( I-ORG
Illinois I-ORG
) I-ORG

Isle B-ORG
of I-ORG
Man I-ORG
Railway I-ORG
stations I-ORG

632 O
, O
Air B-ORG
Force I-ORG
Office I-ORG
of I-ORG
Special I-ORG
Investigations I-ORG

`` O
Gin B-ORG
and I-ORG
Juice I-ORG
'' O

There O
is O
some O
intimation O
that O
Father O
Set O
may O
be O
one O
of O
the O
Great B-ORG
Old I-ORG
Ones I-ORG
that O
H. B-PER
P. I-PER
Lovecraft I-PER
created O
. O

Owl B-PER
Eyes I-PER
– O
`` O
Pumped B-ORG
Up I-ORG
Kicks I-ORG
'' O
( O
Foster B-ORG
the I-ORG
People I-ORG
) O

K B-ORG
( I-ORG
Eighth I-ORG
Avenue I-ORG
Local I-ORG
) I-ORG

' O
'' O
WCAU-TV B-ORG
'' O
' O

List B-ORG
of I-ORG
B-52 I-ORG
Units I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
United I-ORG
States I-ORG
Air I-ORG
Force I-ORG

** O
High B-ORG
Explosive I-ORG
( O
HE O
) O

( O
** O
Represents O
NFL B-ORG
Combine I-ORG
) O

Council B-ORG
of I-ORG
Churches I-ORG
of I-ORG
Malaysia I-ORG

'' O
The B-ORG
Partridge I-ORG
Family I-ORG
'' O

BP B-ORG
Ford I-ORG
Abu I-ORG
Dhabi I-ORG
World I-ORG
Rally I-ORG
Team I-ORG

`` O
Love B-ORG
Needs I-ORG
No I-ORG
Disguise I-ORG
'' O

( O
See O
article O
: O
Entropy B-ORG
( I-ORG
statistical I-ORG
views I-ORG
) I-ORG
) O
. O

''Look O
Out O
, O
Houndour B-ORG
! O

Midnight B-ORG
at I-ORG
Minton I-ORG
's I-ORG
'' O
( O
1941 O
) O

Legal B-ORG
systems I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
world I-ORG

Geneva B-ORG
II I-ORG
Conference I-ORG
on I-ORG
Syria I-ORG

Stoke B-ORG
Bridge I-ORG
, I-ORG
Ipswich I-ORG

Aloha B-ORG
Bowl I-ORG
: O
22 O
Michigan B-LOC
State I-LOC
33 O
, O
23 O
13 O

Palau B-ORG
Municipal I-ORG
d'Esports I-ORG
de I-ORG
Badalona I-ORG

Imperial B-ORG
College I-ORG
Business I-ORG
School I-ORG

53 O
feet O
( O
16 O
m O
) O
- O
Squaw B-ORG
Island I-ORG
Light I-ORG
, O
Michigan B-LOC

U.S. B-ORG
Route I-ORG
211 I-ORG

In O
September O
2011 O
, O
he O
signed O
a O
one-year O
contract O
with O
PAOK B-ORG
in O
Greece B-LOC
. O

Six B-ORG
Celan I-ORG
Songs I-ORG
• I-ORG
The I-ORG
Ballad I-ORG
of I-ORG
Kastriot I-ORG
Rexhepi I-ORG

Drums B-ORG
and I-ORG
Guns I-ORG

In O
1606 O
and O
1607 O
the O
Plymouth B-ORG
Company I-ORG
sent O
ships O
into O
the O
area O
to O
colonize O
, O
but O
the O
settlers O
of O
the O
Popham B-LOC
Colony I-LOC
and O
those O
who O
settled O
along O
the O
Kennebec B-LOC
River I-LOC
returned O
to O
England B-LOC
in O
1608 O
. O

** O
'' O
Kingdom B-ORG
of I-ORG
Pamplona I-ORG
'' O
' O
- O
García B-PER
Sánchez I-PER
II I-PER
( O
994–1004 O
) O

A B-ORG
Dramatic I-ORG
Turn I-ORG
of I-ORG
Events I-ORG
'' O
( O
2011 O
) O

Red B-ORG
Raw I-ORG
& I-ORG
Sore I-ORG
'' O

** O
Aljunied B-ORG
GRC I-ORG
, O
Ang B-ORG
Mo I-ORG
Kio I-ORG
GRC I-ORG
, O
Cheng B-ORG
San I-ORG
GRC I-ORG
, O
Hong B-ORG
Kah I-ORG
GRC I-ORG
were O
increased O
from O
four O
-member O
GRCs O
to O
five-member O
GRCs O
. O

`` O
2 B-ORG
Become I-ORG
1 I-ORG
'' O

Colegio B-ORG
de I-ORG
la I-ORG
Preciosa I-ORG
Sangre I-ORG
de I-ORG
Pichilemu I-ORG

Berliner B-ORG
FC I-ORG
Dynamo I-ORG
( O
6 O
) O

Captain B-ORG
Miša I-ORG
's I-ORG
Mansion I-ORG

The O
album O
's O
lead O
single B-ORG
, O
titled O
`` O
Bounce B-ORG
with I-ORG
Me I-ORG
'' O
was O
released O
on O
August O
8 O
, O
2000 O
. O

*** O
Mountain B-ORG
Standard I-ORG
Time I-ORG
( O
UTC-07 B-ORG
) O
, O
Mountain B-ORG
Daylight I-ORG
Time I-ORG
( O
UTC-06 B-ORG
) O

Vilar B-ORG
do I-ORG
Paraíso I-ORG

Return B-ORG
to I-ORG
the I-ORG
Sea I-ORG

`` O
Ca B-ORG
n't I-ORG
Get I-ORG
You I-ORG
Out I-ORG
of I-ORG
My I-ORG
Head I-ORG
'' O
by O
Kylie B-PER
Minogue I-PER

Celtic B-ORG
Park I-ORG
, O
Glasgow B-LOC
( O
60,832 O
) O

In O
October O
1890 O
, O
uncertain O
of O
his O
destination O
, O
he O
boarded O
the O
Union B-ORG
Pacific I-ORG
Railroad I-ORG
in O
Omaha B-LOC
. O

She O
has O
received O
honorary O
degrees O
from O
the O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Utah I-ORG
, O
Weber B-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
, O
Salt B-ORG
Lake I-ORG
Community I-ORG
College I-ORG
, O
and O
the O
College B-ORG
of I-ORG
Eastern I-ORG
Utah I-ORG
. O

Davao B-LOC
City I-LOC
- O
General B-ORG
Santos I-ORG
City I-ORG

She O
also O
used O
some O
handcrafted O
techniques O
which O
she O
displayed O
at O
the O
1935 O
Brussels B-ORG
International I-ORG
Exhibition I-ORG
. O

Bannered B-ORG
routes I-ORG
of I-ORG
U.S. I-ORG
Route I-ORG
6 I-ORG

W O
, O
New B-ORG
Hampshire I-ORG
Jr. I-ORG
Monarchs I-ORG
( O
EJHL O
) O
2-1 O

Roadway O
flooding O
along O
U.S. B-ORG
Route I-ORG
130 I-ORG
was O
reported O
in O
Collingswood B-LOC
. O

Communist B-ORG
Party I-ORG
of I-ORG
Nepal I-ORG
( I-ORG
UML I-ORG
) I-ORG

' O
'' O
Gisselberg O
'' O
' O
is O
a O
Stadtteil B-ORG
of O
Marburg B-LOC
in O
Hesse B-LOC
. O

The O
main O
opposition O
parties O
of O
Fine B-ORG
Gael I-ORG
and O
the O
Labour B-ORG
Party I-ORG
were O
also O
in O
favour O
. O

File O
: O
Lhasatrainstation O
Lhasa B-ORG
Railway I-ORG
Station I-ORG

He O
appeared O
in O
an O
episode O
of O
Gibbsville B-ORG
'' O
in O
1976 O
. O

30 B-ORG
June I-ORG
- O
Opening O
of O
the O
Prichard B-ORG
Jones I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
at O
Newborough B-LOC
, I-LOC
Anglesey I-LOC
. O

' O
'' O
Daytime B-ORG
Emmy I-ORG
Awards I-ORG
'' O
' O

Maha B-ORG
Sarakham I-ORG
University I-ORG
, O
Thailand B-LOC

Hissar B-ORG
( I-ORG
disambiguation I-ORG
) I-ORG

** O
'' O
Duchy B-LOC
of I-LOC
Gaeta I-LOC
'' O
' O
- O
John B-PER
I I-PER
, O
Hypatus B-ORG
of I-ORG
Gaeta I-ORG
( O
906–933 O
) O

Putties B-ORG
( O
a.k.a O
. O

Shazia B-ORG
Sikander I-ORG
( O
M.F.A O
. O

It O
is O
found O
on O
the O
Galapagos B-ORG
Islands I-ORG
. O

JGC B-ORG
Corporation I-ORG
( O
) O

Two O
tramcars O
survive O
, O
both O
in O
the O
National B-ORG
Tramway I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
collection O
. O

Reed B-ORG
Between I-ORG
the I-ORG
Lines I-ORG
'' O

Prince B-ORG
of I-ORG
Lies I-ORG
'' O
, O
by O
James B-PER
Lowder I-PER
( O
paperback O
, O
August O
1993 O
, O
ISBN O
978-1-56076-626-1 O
; O
paperback O
re-issue O
, O
September O
2003 O
, O
ISBN O
978-0-7869-3114-9 O
) O

Solicitor B-ORG
General I-ORG
for I-ORG
England I-ORG
and I-ORG
Wales I-ORG
– O
Harriet B-PER
Harman I-PER
– O
2001 O

Premier B-ORG
of I-ORG
Newfoundland I-ORG
- O
Clyde B-PER
Wells I-PER

** O
European B-ORG
Astronaut I-ORG
Centre I-ORG
( O
''EAC O
'' O
) O
of O
the O
European B-ORG
Space I-ORG
Agency I-ORG
; O

Interchange B-ORG
( I-ORG
road I-ORG
) I-ORG

Royal B-ORG
Hospital I-ORG
for I-ORG
Sick I-ORG
Children I-ORG
- O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Glasgow I-ORG

Sultan B-ORG
of I-ORG
Johor I-ORG
: O
Sultan B-ORG
Ibrahim I-ORG
Ismail I-ORG

National B-ORG
Gallery I-ORG
of I-ORG
Australia I-ORG

Deportivo B-ORG
Pereira I-ORG
( O
1 O
) O

Strikeforce B-ORG
: I-ORG
Feijao I-ORG
vs. I-ORG
Henderson I-ORG

The O
case O
is O
steeply O
conical O
and O
headspaces B-ORG
on O
the O
conical O
case O
walls O
. O

' O
'' O
Related B-ORG
'' O
' O

Aldeburgh B-ORG
( I-ORG
UK I-ORG
Parliament I-ORG
constituency I-ORG
) I-ORG

There O
are O
currently O
76 O
vehicles O
available O
to O
members O
, O
with O
the O
majority O
of O
them O
located O
in O
Kitchener-Waterloo B-ORG
. O

Tracks B-ORG
( I-ORG
Bruce I-ORG
Springsteen I-ORG
album I-ORG
) I-ORG

Indianapolis B-ORG
, O
Kansas B-LOC
City I-LOC
, O
Portland B-LOC
, O
St. B-LOC
Louis I-LOC
and O
Hartford B-LOC
are O
tied O
with O
three O
each O
. O

Amblyornis B-ORG
inornatus I-ORG
'' O
( O
Vogelkop B-LOC
bowerbird I-LOC
) O

Army B-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Potomac I-ORG

** O
Lars B-ORG
Frederiksen I-ORG
and I-ORG
the I-ORG
Bastards I-ORG
– O
Lars B-ORG
Frederiksen I-ORG
and I-ORG
the I-ORG
Bastards I-ORG
'' O

Chicago B-ORG
Bulls I-ORG
( O
waived O
on O
December O
16 O
) O

`` O
Dead B-ORG
By I-ORG
X-Mas I-ORG
'' O
( O
1981 O
) O

** O
United B-ORG
States I-ORG
Post I-ORG
Office I-ORG
( I-ORG
Jackson I-ORG
Heights I-ORG
, I-ORG
Queens I-ORG
) I-ORG

He O
was O
a O
Democrat B-ORG
. O

' O
'' O
Skindred B-ORG
'' O
' O

; O
*NSYNC B-ORG
– O
No B-ORG
Strings I-ORG
Attached I-ORG
'' O

Common B-ORG
whimbrel I-ORG
, O
''Numenius O
phaeopus O
'' O

'' O
Marians B-PER
Pahars I-PER
'' O
' O
– O
Anorthosis B-ORG
Famagusta I-ORG
FC I-ORG
( O
2006–2007 O
) O

List B-ORG
of I-ORG
number-one I-ORG
singles I-ORG
in I-ORG
2004 I-ORG
( I-ORG
New I-ORG
Zealand I-ORG
) I-ORG

Michael B-PER
Stephens I-PER
, O
Chicago B-ORG
Fire I-ORG

`` O
I B-ORG
'm I-ORG
Addicted I-ORG
'' O

Federation B-ORG
of I-ORG
Norwegian I-ORG
Professional I-ORG
Associations I-ORG

He O
also O
works O
for O
BT B-ORG
Sport I-ORG
as O
an O
analyst O
. O

Museo B-ORG
di I-ORG
Storia I-ORG
Naturale I-ORG
di I-ORG
Venezia I-ORG
, O
Venice B-LOC

Transformers B-ORG
: I-ORG
Prime I-ORG
'' O
( O
2014–present O
) O

** O
''The B-ORG
Bronx I-ORG
'' I-ORG
( I-ORG
2003 I-ORG
album I-ORG
) I-ORG

Widespread O
in O
the O
Central B-LOC
Asia I-LOC
in O
Amu-Darya B-ORG
, O
Zeravshan B-ORG
, O
Syr-Darya B-ORG
, O
and O
Chu B-LOC
River I-LOC
. O

National B-ORG
Federation I-ORG
Party I-ORG
( O
NFP O
) O

Moore B-ORG
House I-ORG
( I-ORG
Winchester I-ORG
, I-ORG
Massachusetts I-ORG
) I-ORG
, O
NRHP-listed O

' O
'' O
Trelleborgs B-ORG
FF I-ORG
'' O
' O

'' O
A B-ORG
Man I-ORG
Alone I-ORG
'' O
- O
Frank B-PER
Sinatra I-PER

Rothes B-ORG
F.C I-ORG
. I-ORG

Eastern B-ORG
span I-ORG
replacement I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
San I-ORG
Francisco–Oakland I-ORG
Bay I-ORG
Bridge I-ORG

Pakistan B-ORG
Air I-ORG
Force I-ORG

`` O
In B-ORG
Pieces I-ORG
'' O
- O
Shannon B-PER
Noll I-PER

'' O
Karneval B-ORG
'' O
, O
Hirato O

El B-ORG
Dorado I-ORG
High I-ORG
School I-ORG
. O

N67 B-ORG
road I-ORG
( I-ORG
Ireland I-ORG
) I-ORG

Moby B-PER
— O
`` O
In B-ORG
My I-ORG
Heart I-ORG
'' O
/ O
Bodyrock B-ORG

The B-ORG
Remote I-ORG
Viewer I-ORG
( O
remastered O
edition O
) O

Jodhpur B-ORG
National I-ORG
University I-ORG

CS B-ORG
Gaz I-ORG
Metan I-ORG
Mediaș I-ORG
( I-ORG
basketball I-ORG
) I-ORG

1936-37 O
Nelson B-ORG
Maple I-ORG
Leafs I-ORG

Founded O
in O
1997 O
, O
CCJ O
was O
formerly O
affiliated O
with O
the O
Columbia B-ORG
School I-ORG
of I-ORG
Journalism I-ORG
. O

'' O
County B-ORG
of I-ORG
Edessa I-ORG
'' O
' O
– O
Joscelin B-PER
II I-PER
( O
1131–1149 O
) O

906th B-ORG
Air I-ORG
Refueling I-ORG
Squadron I-ORG
: O
1 O
February O
1963 O
– O
24 O
July O
1968 O

Jazzmatazz B-ORG
, I-ORG
Vol. I-ORG
3 I-ORG
: I-ORG
Streetsoul I-ORG
'' O

Communist B-ORG
Party I-ORG
of I-ORG
Turkey I-ORG
( I-ORG
disambiguation I-ORG
) I-ORG
, O
for O
other O
groups O
using O
similar O
names O

Joseph B-ORG
Mundasseri I-ORG
( O
1901–1977 O
) O

Inaugural O
winner O
alt=The B-ORG
Cars I-ORG
in I-ORG
1984 I-ORG
. I-ORG

Advertisement O
in O
the O
British B-ORG
Medical I-ORG
Journal I-ORG
, O
April O
11 O
, O
2008 O
. O

Ice B-ORG
cream I-ORG
cake I-ORG

His O
funeral O
took O
place O
in O
his O
hometown O
of O
Cihanbeyli B-LOC
, O
Konya B-LOC
Province I-LOC
and O
was O
attended O
by O
many O
pro-Kurdish O
political O
leaders O
including O
the O
Peoples B-ORG
' I-ORG
Democratic I-ORG
Party I-ORG
( O
HDP O
) O
co-leader O
Selahattin B-PER
Demirtaş I-PER
. O

Between O
1785 O
and O
1818 O
he O
worked O
as O
a O
tutor O
to O
the O
Branicki B-ORG
family O
in O
Białystok B-LOC
. O

' O
'' O
Danish B-ORG
1st I-ORG
Division I-ORG
titles O
: O
' O
'' O

The O
8th B-ORG
Parliament I-ORG
continues O
. O

'' O
Live B-ORG
Is I-ORG
Beautiful I-ORG
'' O
( O
2008 O
) O

''Glider B-ORG
'' I-ORG
( I-ORG
The I-ORG
Sight I-ORG
Below I-ORG
album I-ORG
) I-ORG

Joshua B-ORG
Hempsted I-ORG
House I-ORG

Hell B-ORG
Is I-ORG
Sold I-ORG
Out I-ORG
'' O
( O
1951 O
) O

' O
'' O
Western B-ORG
Samoa I-ORG
'' O
' O

Marian B-ORG
University I-ORG
( I-ORG
Indiana I-ORG
) I-ORG

' O
'' O
Geographic B-ORG
coordinates I-ORG
: O
' O
'' O

'' O
20 B-ORG
/ I-ORG
20 B-ORG
'' O
( O
1978– O
) O

On O
March O
4 O
, O
1897 O
, O
he O
began O
serving O
in O
the O
United B-ORG
States I-ORG
House I-ORG
of I-ORG
Representatives I-ORG
and O
remained O
until O
his O
death O
in O
Washington B-LOC
, I-LOC
D.C I-LOC
. I-LOC
, O
on O
January O
11 O
, O
1903 O
, O
before O
the O
start O
of O
what O
would O
have O
been O
a O
fourth O
term O
. O

Richie B-PER
Sambora I-PER
– O
Stranger B-ORG
in I-ORG
This I-ORG
Town I-ORG
( O
1991 O
) O

St B-ORG
Kilda I-ORG
Road I-ORG
, I-ORG
Melbourne I-ORG

' O
'' O
Earl B-ORG
of I-ORG
Devonshire I-ORG
'' O
' O

** O
Roman B-ORG
Bath I-ORG
rediscovered O
. O

Texas B-ORG
A I-ORG
& I-ORG
M I-ORG
University I-ORG

Bundesliga B-ORG
( O
GER B-ORG
) O

Tour B-ORG
of I-ORG
Poland I-ORG
: O
1994 O

Newmarket B-ORG
Town I-ORG
F.C I-ORG
. I-ORG

Dougherty B-ORG
Valley I-ORG
High I-ORG
School I-ORG

Grateful B-ORG
Dead I-ORG
band O
members O
at O
the O
time O
of O
publication O
were O
Jerry B-PER
Garcia I-PER
, O
Bob B-PER
Weir I-PER
, O
Phil B-PER
Lesh I-PER
, O
Mickey B-PER
Hart I-PER
, O
Bill B-PER
Kreutzmann I-PER
, O
and O
Brent B-PER
Mydland I-PER
. O

Massachusetts B-ORG
Route I-ORG
109 I-ORG

'' O
Oxyptilus B-ORG
chordites I-ORG
'' O
Meyrick O
, O
1913 O

2002 O
: O
New B-ORG
York I-ORG
Liberty I-ORG

Iran B-ORG
Pro I-ORG
League I-ORG
( O
2 O
) O
: O
2005–06 B-LOC
, O
2008–09 B-LOC

Escape B-ORG
from I-ORG
the I-ORG
Island I-ORG
of I-ORG
Aquarius I-ORG
'' O
( O
1986 O
) O

Ignorance O
( O
avidya B-ORG
'' O
) O

Soviet B-ORG
Top I-ORG
League I-ORG
runner-up O
: O
1987 O
, O
1990 O

Indian B-LOC
Ocean I-LOC
, O
Rodrigues B-ORG
Island I-ORG

Embassy B-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
United I-ORG
States I-ORG
, I-ORG
Oslo I-ORG

List B-ORG
of I-ORG
lakes I-ORG
in I-ORG
Norway I-ORG

'' O
Sex B-ORG
and I-ORG
the I-ORG
City I-ORG
'' O

St B-ORG
Oswald I-ORG
's I-ORG
Church I-ORG
, I-ORG
Ravenstonedale I-ORG

Going O
into O
the O
1985 B-ORG
NBA I-ORG
Draft I-ORG
, O
the O
Chicago B-ORG
Bulls I-ORG
, O
Atlanta B-ORG
Hawks I-ORG
, O
Golden B-ORG
State I-ORG
Warriors I-ORG
, O

Label O
: O
BNA B-ORG
Records I-ORG

===With O
Frida B-PER
Lyngstad I-PER
( O
ABBA B-ORG
) O
=== O

George B-PER
MacDonald I-PER
– O
The B-ORG
Princess I-ORG
and I-ORG
Curdie I-ORG
'' O

`` O
Fire B-ORG
and I-ORG
Rain I-ORG
'' O

' O
'' O
Vermont B-LOC
'' O
' O
– O
Thomas B-PER
Chittenden I-PER
, O
Governor B-ORG
of I-ORG
Vermont I-ORG
( O
13 O
March O
1778 O
– O
13 O
October O
1789 O
) O

On O
1955-02-19 O
he O
was O
nominated O
by O
President B-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
United I-ORG
States I-ORG
Dwight B-PER
D. I-PER
Eisenhower I-PER
for O
the O
position O
of O
Assistant B-ORG
Secretary I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Army I-ORG
( I-ORG
Financial I-ORG
Management I-ORG
and I-ORG
Comptroller I-ORG
) I-ORG
. O

'' O
The B-ORG
New I-ORG
Scooby I-ORG
and I-ORG
Scrappy-Doo I-ORG
Show I-ORG
'' O

She O
worked O
on O
the O
Chester B-ORG
Chronicle I-ORG
. O

D O
( O
Denver B-ORG
Mint I-ORG
in O
Denver B-ORG
, I-ORG
Colorado I-ORG
) O

Mars B-ORG
Desert I-ORG
Research I-ORG
Station I-ORG

Clitheroe B-ORG
Advertiser I-ORG
and I-ORG
Times I-ORG

She O
is O
of O
Armenian B-ORG
descent O
. O

Workers B-ORG
' I-ORG
Stadium I-ORG
, O
Beijing B-LOC

'' O
Having B-ORG
a I-ORG
Party I-ORG
'' O
( O
1982 O
) O

Progress B-ORG
Party I-ORG
( I-ORG
Norway I-ORG
) I-ORG

Ca B-ORG
Bau I-ORG
Kan I-ORG
'' O
( O
2001 O
) O

List B-ORG
of I-ORG
Kings I-ORG
of I-ORG
Strathclyde I-ORG

U.S. B-ORG
Army I-ORG
Corps I-ORG
of I-ORG
Engineers I-ORG
Vessel I-ORG
Yard I-ORG

1995 B-ORG
World I-ORG
Rally I-ORG
Championship I-ORG

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Warwick I-ORG
, O
1983 O

Washington B-ORG
State I-ORG
Route I-ORG
542 I-ORG

Green B-ORG
Party I-ORG
of I-ORG
England I-ORG
and I-ORG
Wales I-ORG

Packed B-ORG
to I-ORG
the I-ORG
Rafters I-ORG
'' O

Soothe O
was O
sold O
to O
Bausch B-ORG
& I-ORG
Lomb I-ORG
in O
August O
2007 O
. O

The B-ORG
Columbus I-ORG
Citizen-Journal I-ORG
'' O

She O
first O
won O
notice O
singing O
with O
Big B-PER
Tiny I-PER
Little I-PER
in O
the O
early O
1970s O
, O
but O
became O
internationally O
known O
in O
1974 O
when O
she O
played O
Bessie B-PER
Smith I-PER
( O
to O
whom O
she O
is O
of O
no O
relation O
) O
in O
Dick B-PER
Hyman I-PER
's O
''Satchmo O
Remembered O
'' O
at O
Carnegie B-ORG
Hall I-ORG
. O

*2014 O
: O
`` O
Black B-ORG
Widow I-ORG
'' O
( O
Iggy B-PER
Azalea I-PER
) O
' O
'' O
1 O
'' O
' O

President B-ORG
: O
Enrique B-PER
Peña I-PER
Nieto I-PER

In O
1935 O
, O
he O
took O
a O
faculty O
position O
at O
Hosei B-ORG
University I-ORG
. O

'' O
My B-ORG
Heart I-ORG
Will I-ORG
Go I-ORG
On I-ORG
'' O
by O
Celine B-PER
Dion I-PER
( O
1998 O
) O

The B-ORG
Visitors I-ORG
'' O
( O
1981 O
) O

Currently O
, O
she O
's O
employed O
at O
United B-ORG
Media I-ORG
. O

Psychiatric B-ORG
treatments I-ORG
have O
changed O
over O
the O
past O
several O
decades O
. O

'' O
The B-ORG
Memory I-ORG
of I-ORG
Trees I-ORG
'' O

Gibraltar B-ORG
at I-ORG
the I-ORG
Commonwealth I-ORG
Games I-ORG

He O
interned O
for O
State B-ORG
Assemblyman I-ORG
and O
current O
U.S. B-ORG
Representative I-ORG
Brian B-PER
Higgins I-PER
. O

Janata B-ORG
Dal I-ORG
( I-ORG
United I-ORG
) I-ORG

He O
has O
also O
played O
in O
the O
Scottish B-ORG
Premier I-ORG
League I-ORG
for O
Celtic B-ORG
and O
Aberdeen B-ORG
and O
in O
the O
Football B-ORG
League I-ORG
with O
Swindon B-ORG
Town I-ORG
, O
Millwall B-ORG
, O
Cardiff B-ORG
City I-ORG
, O
Leeds B-ORG
United I-ORG
, O
Norwich B-ORG
City I-ORG
, O
Barnsley B-ORG
, O
Leicester B-ORG
City I-ORG
, O
Charlton B-ORG
Athletic I-ORG
, O
Scunthorpe B-ORG
United I-ORG
and O
Tranmere B-ORG
Rovers I-ORG
. O

Halle B-ORG
( I-ORG
Westf I-ORG
) I-ORG
station I-ORG

' O
'' O
Trois B-ORG
Hommes I-ORG
à I-ORG
Abattre I-ORG
'' O
' O
'' O

This O
is O
true O
for O
Republicans B-ORG
as O
well O
. O

It O
was O
dedicated O
to O
Saint B-ORG
Mary I-ORG
and O
Saint B-PER
Martial I-PER
. O

From O
1954 O
to O
1959 O
, O
he O
was O
a O
member O
of O
the O
faculty O
at O
Ohio B-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
before O
moving O
to O
the O
Lawrence B-ORG
Berkeley I-ORG
National I-ORG
Laboratory I-ORG
where O
he O
served O
as O
Lab O
Director O
in O
1973-80 O
. O

Carolina B-ORG
Dodge I-ORG
Dealers I-ORG
400 I-ORG

`` O
Oki B-ORG
Doki I-ORG
Doc I-ORG
'' O
( O
1996 O
) O

`` O
We B-ORG
Exist I-ORG
'' O
– O
Arcade B-ORG
Fire I-ORG

In O
1988 O
he O
had O
a O
short O
attachment O
to O
Sunday B-ORG
Sequence I-ORG
as O
presenter O
. O

Fangavaktin B-ORG
'' O
( O
2009 O
) O
( O
TV-series O
) O
as O
Emilía O

Stéphane B-PER
N'Guéma I-PER
– O
Rennes B-ORG
– O
2002–07 O

*2005 O
: O
Intelligence B-ORG
Failure I-ORG
'' O

** O
'' O
'Gaihawk O
'' O
' O
- O
MiG-29 B-ORG
Fulcrum I-ORG
'' O

It O
is O
found O
in O
Greece B-LOC
( O
Rodhos B-ORG
) O
, O
Turkey B-LOC
and O
Israel B-LOC
. O

Quebec B-ORG
Route I-ORG
361 I-ORG

Warner B-ORG
Music I-ORG
picked O
on O
that O
and O
signed O
her O
reissuing O
the O
album O
with O
two O
additional O
tracks O
. O

Ek B-ORG
Vivah I-ORG
Aisa I-ORG
Bhi I-ORG
'' O

Supreme B-ORG
Assembly I-ORG
( I-ORG
Uzbekistan I-ORG
) I-ORG

Sang B-ORG
Doo I-ORG
! I-ORG
Let I-ORG
's I-ORG
Go I-ORG
to I-ORG
School I-ORG
'' O

This O
is O
often O
not O
the O
case O
( O
see O
conformity B-ORG
) O
. O

Premier B-ORG
of I-ORG
Tasmania I-ORG
— O
Francis B-PER
Smith I-PER

Hammond B-ORG
Heroes I-ORG
( O
2006 O
) O
– O
NIFL B-ORG

Thrills B-ORG
, I-ORG
Kills I-ORG
& I-ORG
Sunday I-ORG
Pills I-ORG
'' O

United B-ORG
States I-ORG
Senate I-ORG
Subcommittee I-ORG
on I-ORG
Internal I-ORG
Security I-ORG

'' O
Aoi B-ORG
Sekai I-ORG
no I-ORG
Chūshin I-ORG
de I-ORG
'' O
– O
Tejirof O

Clayton-Hamilton B-ORG
Jazz I-ORG
Orchestra I-ORG

Jis B-ORG
Desh I-ORG
Mein I-ORG
Ganga I-ORG
Behti I-ORG
Hai I-ORG

Antonio B-PER
Vojak I-PER
( O
Napoli B-ORG
) O

Cesar B-ORG
Ortiz I-ORG
– O
FC B-ORG
Vaslui I-ORG
– O
2013–2014 O

'' O
3 O
'' O
( O
1996 O
) O
- O
Lithium B-ORG

Richard B-ORG
Ortner I-ORG
( O
1998present O
) O

In O
other O
discussions O
with O
the O
political O
leadership O
– O
including O
( O
German B-ORG
Chancellor I-ORG
ret O
. O

at O
St. B-ORG
Andrews I-ORG
University I-ORG
in O
1862 O
. O

at O
the O
2005 B-ORG
Southeast I-ORG
Asian I-ORG
Games I-ORG
in O
the O
Philippines B-LOC
. O

On O
22 O
, O
24 O
and O
26 O
May O
2012 O
she O
hosted O
the O
Eurovision B-ORG
Song I-ORG
Contest I-ORG
2012 I-ORG
in O
Baku B-LOC
, O
Azerbaijan B-LOC
together O
with O
Eldar B-PER
Gasimov I-PER
and O
Nargiz B-PER
Birk-Petersen I-PER
. O

Halt B-ORG
and I-ORG
Catch I-ORG
Fire I-ORG
( I-ORG
TV I-ORG
series I-ORG
) I-ORG

Rishton B-ORG
Ke I-ORG
Bhanwar I-ORG
Mein I-ORG
Uljhi I-ORG
Niyati I-ORG
'' O

Brown B-ORG
Mackie I-ORG
College I-ORG

Father B-ORG
Murphy I-ORG
'' O
( O
1981–1983 O
) O

' O
'' O
VfB B-ORG
Stuttgart I-ORG
0–0 O
'' O
' O

The O
first O
World B-LOC
Series I-LOC
was O
played O
between O
the O
Boston B-ORG
Americans I-ORG
and O
Pittsburgh B-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
. O

Transferred O
to O
Steve B-PER
O'Shea I-PER
of O
Auckland B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
on O
August O
25 O
. O

** O
Development B-ORG
– O
continuation O
and O
improvement O
of O
a O
designed O
solution O

`` O
Big B-ORG
Spender I-ORG
'' O
( O
Peggy B-PER
Lee I-PER
) O

Sponsored O
by O
NZ B-ORG
On I-ORG
Air I-ORG

In O
2001 O
, O
he O
began O
working O
on O
the O
follow-up O
for O
''Twilight O
'' O
tentatively O
titled O
Amber B-ORG
Headlights I-ORG
'' O
. O

Muzik]] O
'' O
( O
4Minute B-ORG
) O

Bellevue B-ORG
Downtown I-ORG
Park I-ORG
: O
2015 O

Helen B-ORG
Bernstein I-ORG
High I-ORG
School I-ORG

2nd B-ORG
Cavalry I-ORG
Division I-ORG
Emanuele I-ORG
Filiberto I-ORG
Testa I-ORG
di I-ORG
Ferro I-ORG

: O
Vuelta B-ORG
a I-ORG
España I-ORG
: O

She O
was O
the O
2004 O
Chicago B-ORG
Marathon I-ORG
winner O
. O

FC B-ORG
Stade I-ORG
Nyonnais I-ORG
( O
VD B-LOC
) O

''Sardinia O
'' O
Vell B-ORG
. I-ORG
= O
Guettarda B-LOC
'' O

Saturday B-ORG
Morning I-ORG
: I-ORG
Cartoons I-ORG
' I-ORG
Greatest I-ORG
Hits I-ORG

`` O
I B-ORG
Want I-ORG
to I-ORG
Hold I-ORG
Your I-ORG
Hand I-ORG
'' O
/ O
`` O
Twist B-ORG
and I-ORG
Shout I-ORG
'' O
/ O
`` O
Hey B-ORG
Jude I-ORG
'' O

Ministry B-ORG
of I-ORG
Education I-ORG
( I-ORG
Pakistan I-ORG
) I-ORG

The O
Tuskegee B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
is O
founded O

Continente B-ORG
( I-ORG
Supermarket I-ORG
) I-ORG

Royal B-ORG
Inniskilling I-ORG
Fusiliers I-ORG

El B-ORG
cuerpo I-ORG
del I-ORG
deseo I-ORG
'' O

Kawasaki B-ORG
Z I-ORG
( I-ORG
disambiguation I-ORG
) I-ORG

People B-ORG
's I-ORG
Party I-ORG
( I-ORG
Dalmatia I-ORG
) I-ORG

Pursuit B-ORG
of I-ORG
Happiness I-ORG
( I-ORG
song I-ORG
) I-ORG

Mile B-LOC
High I-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
– O
Denver B-ORG
, I-ORG
Colorado I-ORG
( O
1948–2000 O
) O

LoLo B-ORG
Jones I-ORG
' O
'' O
' O

One O
year O
later O
, O
it O
was O
accepted O
into O
the O
Association B-ORG
of I-ORG
Alternative I-ORG
Newsweeklies I-ORG
. O

** O
Ros B-ORG
na I-ORG
Rún I-ORG
'' O

Universidad B-ORG
Autónoma I-ORG
de I-ORG
Tamaulipas I-ORG
- O
Ciudad B-LOC
Victoria I-LOC

'' O
Revivor B-ORG
'' O
( O
2003 O
) O
( O
remix O
album O
) O

List B-ORG
of I-ORG
accolades I-ORG
received I-ORG
by I-ORG
the I-ORG
Predator I-ORG
franchise I-ORG

They O
were O
redesignated O
' O
'' O
VO-4M O
'' O
' O
on O
May O
29 O
, O
1922 O
and O
returned O
to O
Marine B-ORG
Corps I-ORG
Base I-ORG
Quantico I-ORG
in O
1924 O
. O

Castleton B-ORG
Garland I-ORG
Day I-ORG
( O
Castleton B-LOC
) O

Virginia B-ORG
State I-ORG
Route I-ORG
152 I-ORG

' O
'' O
Honda B-ORG
'' O
' O

Days B-ORG
of I-ORG
Our I-ORG
Lives I-ORG
'' O

Thai B-ORG
football I-ORG
records I-ORG
and I-ORG
statistics I-ORG

Hebrew B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Jerusalem I-ORG

The B-ORG
Storm I-ORG
- O
closed O
20 O
January O
2006 O

Pharmaceutical B-ORG
Society I-ORG
of I-ORG
Northern I-ORG
Ireland I-ORG

Greenwood B-ORG
Furnace I-ORG
State I-ORG
Park I-ORG
( O
Huntingdon B-LOC
County I-LOC
) O

Kizz B-ORG
My I-ORG
Black I-ORG
Azz I-ORG
'' O

Don B-ORG
Bosco I-ORG
Preparatory I-ORG
High I-ORG
School I-ORG
( O
Ramsey B-LOC
) O

He O
made O
his O
debut O
on O
8 O
September O
in O
a O
5–0 O
win O
over O
Consett B-ORG
. O

105.3 O
MHz O
SBS B-ORG
Radio I-ORG
– O
SBS B-ORG

Al B-PER
Barr I-PER
, O
vocalist O
for O
Dropkick B-ORG
Murphys I-ORG

Firefighter B-ORG
Assist I-ORG
and I-ORG
Search I-ORG
Team I-ORG

Bessborough B-ORG
School I-ORG
- O
Moncton B-LOC
( O
K-8 O
) O

'' O
The B-ORG
Puppet I-ORG
Master I-ORG
'' O
( O
2003 O
) O

Patriot B-ORG
( I-ORG
disambiguation I-ORG
) I-ORG

Claude B-ORG
Antoine I-ORG
Valdec I-ORG
de I-ORG
Lessart I-ORG

** O
Central B-ORG
Stadium I-ORG
( I-ORG
Volgograd I-ORG
) I-ORG
built O
. O

*Wazzu O
- O
Washington B-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG

`` O
Fall B-ORG
Back I-ORG
Down I-ORG
'' O

Jakob B-PER
( O
6 O
June O
1471 O
– O
27 O
April O
1511 O
, O
Cologne B-LOC
) O
, O
Archbishop B-ORG
of I-ORG
Trier I-ORG

: O
Oman B-ORG
Professional I-ORG
League I-ORG
( O
1 O
) O
: O
2014–15 B-LOC

Groupama B-ORG
3 I-ORG
was O
the O
first O
to O
finish O
in O
9 O
days O
, O
3 O
hours O
, O
14 O
minutes O
and O
47 O
seconds O
. O

Deutschland-Preis B-ORG
- O
( O
1 O
) O
- O
''Luso O
( O
1997 O
) O
'' O

Derick B-ORG
Thompson I-ORG
( O
unknown O
) O

Iowa B-ORG
John I-ORG
Deere I-ORG
Dealers I-ORG
250 I-ORG

Lanchester B-ORG
's I-ORG
laws I-ORG

'' O
Armenian B-ORG
National I-ORG
Congress I-ORG
'' O
' O
— O
Vahagn B-PER
Khachatryan I-PER

Andy B-PER
Williams I-PER
– O
Warm B-ORG
and I-ORG
Willing I-ORG
'' O

Jacques B-ORG
Bizard I-ORG
Bridge I-ORG

Avant B-ORG
que I-ORG
l'ombre I-ORG
... I-ORG
'' O

It O
should O
be O
noted O
, O
however O
, O
that O
the O
story O
is O
being O
told O
by O
Mr. B-ORG
Mxyzptlk I-ORG
, O
and O
may O
therefore O
be O
completely O
untrue O
. O

anything O
related O
to O
Somalis B-ORG
or O
Somalia B-LOC

Brinley B-ORG
Richards I-ORG
( O
1904-1981 O
) O

Anarchist B-ORG
Federation I-ORG
( I-ORG
Britain I-ORG
and I-ORG
Ireland I-ORG
) I-ORG
1986–Present O

Warlord B-ORG
( I-ORG
Star I-ORG
Trek I-ORG
: I-ORG
Voyager I-ORG
) I-ORG

57th B-ORG
Infantry I-ORG
Regiment I-ORG
( I-ORG
Ottoman I-ORG
Empire I-ORG
) I-ORG

Iván B-ORG
Amaya I-ORG
– O
Apollon B-ORG
Limassol I-ORG
( O
2012 O
) O

Some O
of O
the O
set O
trimmings O
and O
a O
stage O
coach O
came O
from O
the O
Hell B-ORG
on I-ORG
Wheels I-ORG
'' O
set O
. O

U.S. B-ORG
Route I-ORG
181 I-ORG

Headquartered O
in O
Fredericksburg B-ORG
, I-ORG
VA I-ORG
, O
Marstel-Day O
operates O
11 O
offices O
in O
all O
, O
including O
locations O
in O
California B-LOC
, O
Colorado B-LOC
, O
Maryland B-LOC
, O
Mississippi B-LOC
, O
Texas B-LOC
, O
and O
the O
United B-LOC
Kingdom I-LOC
. O

Seibert B-ORG
Stadium I-ORG
• O
Homewood B-ORG
, I-ORG
AL I-ORG

The O
album O
features O
guitarist O
Larry B-PER
LaLonde I-PER
and O
bassist O
Les B-PER
Claypool I-PER
before O
they O
went O
on O
to O
work O
on O
Primus B-ORG
and O
was O
produced O
by O
Metallica B-ORG
guitarist O
Kirk B-PER
Hammett I-PER
. O

Boogiest B-ORG
Band I-ORG
In I-ORG
Town I-ORG

*November O
8 O
– O
Countdown B-ORG
'' O
on O
the O
Australian B-ORG
Broadcasting I-ORG
Corporation I-ORG
( O
1974–87 O
) O

'' O
Signifyin B-ORG
' I-ORG
'' O
( O
1963 O
) O

Lincoln-Herndon B-ORG
Law I-ORG
Offices I-ORG
State I-ORG
Historic I-ORG
Site I-ORG

In O
retirement O
he O
became O
involved O
in O
the O
governance O
of O
Higher B-ORG
Education I-ORG
. O

He O
currently O
lives O
in O
Napoli B-ORG
, O
Italy B-LOC
. O

Blue B-ORG
Grass I-ORG
Council I-ORG
— O
Lexington B-LOC
, I-LOC
Kentucky I-LOC

Kong B-ORG
: I-ORG
The I-ORG
Animated I-ORG
Series I-ORG
'' O

Angola B-ORG
women I-ORG
's I-ORG
national I-ORG
under-16 I-ORG
and I-ORG
under-17 I-ORG
basketball I-ORG
team I-ORG

West B-ORG
Florida I-ORG
Argonauts I-ORG

Effects B-ORG
of I-ORG
mach I-ORG
number I-ORG
and I-ORG
shock I-ORG
losses I-ORG
in I-ORG
turbomachines I-ORG

Hôtel-Dieu B-ORG
of I-ORG
Carpentras I-ORG

Southern B-ORG
Knights I-ORG
'' O
35-36 O
( O
1992 O
) O

List B-ORG
of I-ORG
Swedish I-ORG
football I-ORG
transfers I-ORG
winter I-ORG
2009–2010 I-ORG

Aboriginal B-ORG
Peoples I-ORG
Party I-ORG
of I-ORG
Canada I-ORG

WHEC-TV B-ORG
in O
Rochester B-LOC
, I-LOC
New I-LOC
York I-LOC

Thames B-ORG
Ironworks I-ORG
F.C. I-ORG
season I-ORG
1897-98 I-ORG

New B-ORG
Jersey I-ORG
State I-ORG
Bar I-ORG
Association I-ORG

** O
North B-ORG
Dakota I-ORG
Department I-ORG
of I-ORG
Transportation I-ORG

1907 O
- O
1914 O
A. B-ORG
R. I-ORG
Banerjee I-ORG

Dito B-PER
is O
a O
successful O
writer O
in O
Los B-ORG
Angeles I-ORG
. O

Ladies B-ORG
singles I-ORG
( I-ORG
disambiguation I-ORG
) I-ORG

A10 B-ORG
road I-ORG
( I-ORG
England I-ORG
) I-ORG

King B-ORG
's I-ORG
Cross I-ORG
St. I-ORG
Pancras I-ORG
tube I-ORG
station I-ORG

** O
Church B-ORG
Village I-ORG
railway I-ORG
station I-ORG

** O
Lister B-ORG
Mills I-ORG
founded O
in O
Manningham B-LOC
. O

Charles B-ORG
de I-ORG
Gaulle I-ORG
– I-ORG
Étoile I-ORG

Inwood B-ORG
– I-ORG
207th I-ORG
Street I-ORG
( I-ORG
IND I-ORG
Eighth I-ORG
Avenue I-ORG
Line I-ORG
) I-ORG

Glasnost B-ORG
( I-ORG
album I-ORG
) I-ORG

*1280 O
/ O
WPKZ B-ORG
: O
Fitchburg B-LOC

He O
spent O
at O
least O
four O
seasons O
in O
the O
American B-ORG
Soccer I-ORG
League I-ORG
, O
three O
in O
the O
North B-ORG
American I-ORG
Soccer I-ORG
League I-ORG
and O
four O
in O
the O
Major B-ORG
Indoor I-ORG
Soccer I-ORG
League I-ORG
. O

' O
'' O
Morbidelli B-ORG
'' O
' O

Loose B-ORG
'' O
( O
1995 O
) O

Stéphane B-PER
Galland I-PER
( O
Aka B-ORG
Moon I-ORG
, O
Zap B-ORG
Mama I-ORG
, O
Octurn B-ORG
) O

Prior O
to O
decommissioning O
, O
it O
was O
possible O
for O
Beaver B-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
to O
become O
honorary O
members O
of O
the O
crew O
. O

Bishopric B-ORG
of I-ORG
Constance I-ORG

As O
the O
motto O
goes O
, O
‘Every O
punch B-ORG
, O
every O
week O
, O
since O
1909.’ O

Thank B-ORG
U I-ORG
'' O
single O
( O
bonus O
track O
) O

Darren B-PER
Keet I-PER
''Wits O
'' O
( O
currently O
at O
KV B-ORG
Kortrijk I-ORG
) O

Holy B-ORG
Trinity I-ORG
Ukrainian I-ORG
Orthodox I-ORG
Cathedral I-ORG
( I-ORG
Vancouver I-ORG
) I-ORG

John B-ORG
Fell I-ORG
( I-ORG
clergyman I-ORG
) I-ORG
( O
1625–1686 O
) O

Object B-ORG
relations I-ORG
'' O
: O
The O
capacity O
for O
mutually O
satisfying O
relationship O
. O

Its O
local B-ORG
government I-ORG
area I-ORG
is O
the O
City B-LOC
of I-LOC
Port I-LOC
Phillip I-LOC
. O

Columbus-Auburn-Opelika B-ORG
, I-ORG
GA-AL I-ORG
Combined I-ORG
Statistical I-ORG
Area I-ORG

** O
April O
: O
Shanghai B-ORG
Volunteer I-ORG
Corps I-ORG
organized O
. O

' O
'' O
CHEX-TV-2 B-ORG
22 O
'' O
' O

San B-ORG
Jose-Sunnyvale-Santa I-ORG
Clara I-ORG
, I-ORG
CA I-ORG
MSA I-ORG

Deputy B-ORG
Prime I-ORG
Minister I-ORG
of I-ORG
Turkey I-ORG

Dukes B-ORG
of I-ORG
Brittany I-ORG
family I-ORG
tree I-ORG

Mondawmin B-ORG
Metro I-ORG
Subway I-ORG
Station I-ORG
( O
SB O
) O

It O
was O
contested O
by O
England B-ORG
, O
France B-ORG
, O
Ireland B-ORG
, O
Scotland B-ORG
and O
Wales B-ORG
. O

GEMA B-ORG
( I-ORG
Germany I-ORG
) I-ORG

Partnoy B-ORG
, I-ORG
Frank I-ORG
. O

British B-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Electric I-ORG
Railway I-ORG

The O
London B-LOC
Mithraeum I-LOC
was O
rededicated O
, O
probably O
to O
Bacchus B-ORG
. O

Live B-ORG
'' O
by O
The B-ORG
Mars I-ORG
Volta I-ORG

In O
the O
First O
Round O
, O
they O
lost O
to O
Liverpool B-ORG
FC I-ORG
( O
lost O
0-3 O
away O
, O
0-1 O
at O
home O
) O
. O

website O
for O
Independent B-ORG
Lens I-ORG
'' O
on O
PBS B-ORG

Valley B-ORG
Hills I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
– O
Hickory B-LOC

( O
Compare O
Covenanting B-ORG
and O
Established B-ORG
Church I-ORG
. O

Delta B-ORG
Sigma I-ORG
Epsilon I-ORG

Sideways B-ORG
( I-ORG
Clarence I-ORG
Greenwood I-ORG
song I-ORG
) I-ORG

In O
2011 O
, O
the O
track O
was O
used O
on O
a O
commercial O
for O
Pukka B-ORG
Pies I-ORG
in O
the O
UK B-LOC
. O

Make B-ORG
Your I-ORG
Mark I-ORG
: I-ORG
Ultimate I-ORG
Playlist I-ORG

1910–11 B-ORG
Dumbarton I-ORG
F.C. I-ORG
season I-ORG

'' O
Outside B-ORG
the I-ORG
Lines I-ORG
First I-ORG
Report I-ORG
'' O
( O
since O
2006 O
) O

743–750 O
Third B-ORG
Islamic I-ORG
Civil I-ORG
War I-ORG

Besides O
contributing O
critically O
to O
the O
Chicago B-ORG
Dial B-ORG
'' O
, O
he O
published O
: O

RC B-ORG
Lechia I-ORG
Gdańsk I-ORG

**Game O
2 O
in O
Chiba B-ORG
: O
Pacific B-ORG
League I-ORG
4 O
, O
Central B-ORG
League I-ORG
3 O
. O

Pieniny B-ORG
National I-ORG
Park I-ORG
( I-ORG
Poland I-ORG
) I-ORG

*2006 O
– O
There B-ORG
Be I-ORG
Squabbles I-ORG
Ahead I-ORG
'' O
– O
Stolen B-ORG
Babies I-ORG

`` O
once O
removed O
'' O
or O
`` O
twice O
removed O
'' O
- O
see O
Cousin B-ORG
chart I-ORG

İstanbulspor B-ORG
A.Ş I-ORG
. I-ORG

**2007 O
: O
Mixtape B-ORG
Messiah I-ORG
3 I-ORG
'' O

Swedish-Norwegian B-ORG
War I-ORG
( I-ORG
1814 I-ORG
) I-ORG

Ingram B-ORG
Hill I-ORG
( O
active O
; O
unsigned O
) O

Grand B-ORG
Island I-ORG
Army I-ORG
Airfield I-ORG
, O
Nebraska B-LOC
, O
8 O
September O
1945 O
– O
4 O
August O
1946 O

Collocalia B-ORG
orientalis I-ORG
'' O
( O
Mayr B-LOC
's I-LOC
swiftlet I-LOC
) O

It O
is O
marked O
by O
the O
sign O
once O
used O
by O
Orient B-ORG
Express I-ORG
, O
which O
was O
demolished O
in O
2003 O
. O

The B-ORG
Barna I-ORG
Group I-ORG

Holden B-ORG
VL I-ORG
Commodore I-ORG
SS I-ORG
Group I-ORG
A I-ORG
SV I-ORG

2000 B-ORG
Men I-ORG
's I-ORG
Olympic I-ORG
Games I-ORG
100m I-ORG
Breaststroke I-ORG
( I-ORG
Sydney I-ORG
) I-ORG

Kempten B-LOC
, O
Bayern B-ORG
, O
Germany B-LOC

One B-ORG
of I-ORG
These I-ORG
Nights I-ORG

It O
is O
headquartered O
in O
Ansan B-LOC
, O
Gyeonggi-do B-ORG
. O

Alun B-ORG
Davies I-ORG
( I-ORG
disambiguation I-ORG
) I-ORG

National B-ORG
Museum I-ORG
of I-ORG
Language I-ORG

Coverage O
of O
the O
1987 B-ORG
stock I-ORG
market I-ORG
crash I-ORG

: O
:1st O
Round O
7 O
( O
Hafjell B-ORG
, O
Norway B-LOC
) O

It O
was O
released O
on O
June O
7 O
, O
2011 O
, O
by O
Strange B-ORG
Music I-ORG
. O

The O
differences O
between O
the O
two O
were O
defined O
in O
1977 O
by O
United B-ORG
States I-ORG
federal I-ORG
judge I-ORG
James B-PER
Marshall I-PER
Carter I-PER
in O
Sid B-ORG
& I-ORG
Marty I-ORG
Krofft I-ORG
Television I-ORG
Productions I-ORG
, I-ORG
Inc. I-ORG
v. I-ORG
McDonald I-ORG
's I-ORG
Corp I-ORG
. I-ORG
'' O
: O

To O
New B-ORG
Jersey I-ORG
Devils I-ORG
Jeff B-PER
Friesen I-PER
Oleg B-PER
Tverdovsky I-PER
Maxim B-PER
Balmochnykh I-PER

Highland B-ORG
School I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG

'' O
Passe B-ORG
ton I-ORG
bac I-ORG
d'abord I-ORG
'' O
( O
''Graduate O
First O
'' O
) O
( O
1979 O
) O

; O
Royal B-ORG
Danish I-ORG
Air I-ORG
Force I-ORG

'' O
I B-ORG
'm I-ORG
a I-ORG
Hustla I-ORG
'' O
( O
2005 O
) O

A B-ORG
Certain I-ORG
Magical I-ORG
Index I-ORG
'' O

However O
his O
stay O
at O
Saltergate B-ORG
lasted O
only O
four O
months O
, O
making O
16 O
appearances O
in O
total O
before O
joining O
Derby B-ORG
County I-ORG
in O
January O
1956 O
for O
a O
fee O
of O
£1,500 O
. O

' O
'' O
Ivy B-PER
Queen I-PER
'' O
' O
- O
' O
'' O
Drama B-ORG
Queen I-ORG
Deluxe I-ORG
Edition I-ORG
'' O
' O

`` O
Wave B-ORG
'' O
( O
Antonio B-PER
Carlos I-PER
Jobim I-PER
) O
- O
6:07 O

Brașov B-LOC
– O
Sfântu B-LOC
Gheorghe I-LOC
– O
Băile B-LOC
Tușnad I-LOC
– O
Miercurea-Ciuc B-ORG
– O
Toplița B-LOC

ISU B-ORG
JGP I-ORG
Minsk I-ORG
Ice I-ORG
2009 I-ORG

Aimophila B-ORG
botterii I-ORG
'' O
( O
Botteri B-LOC
's I-LOC
sparrow I-LOC
) O

1979 O
- O
Essen B-ORG
City I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
built O
. O

''Dějiny O
knížetství B-ORG
Těšínského I-ORG
'' O
( O
1894 O
) O

Shri B-ORG
Swaminarayan I-ORG
Mandir I-ORG
, I-ORG
Mumbai I-ORG

Panathinaikos B-ORG
F.C I-ORG
. I-ORG

Rajasthan B-ORG
Legislative I-ORG
Assembly I-ORG
election I-ORG
, I-ORG
1951 I-ORG

It O
is O
in O
size O
, O
with O
a O
population O
of O
171 O
( O
INE B-ORG
2006 O
) O
. O

`` O
Love B-ORG
It I-ORG
When I-ORG
You I-ORG
Call I-ORG
'' O

12 O
- O
RW O
Rick B-PER
Middleton I-PER
( O
Boston B-ORG
Bruins I-ORG
) O

He O
grew O
up O
in O
Bellevue B-LOC
, I-LOC
Washington I-LOC
and O
attended O
Interlake B-ORG
High I-ORG
School I-ORG
. O

El B-ORG
Fureidis I-ORG
in O
Montecito B-LOC
, I-LOC
California I-LOC
, O
1906 O

'' O
5 B-ORG
Seconds I-ORG
of I-ORG
Summer I-ORG
'' O
' O

'' O
Chom B-ORG
Phon I-ORG
'' O
( O
Thailand B-LOC
) O

Blue B-ORG
Heron I-ORG
Park I-ORG
Preserve I-ORG

' O
'' O
Aprilia B-ORG
'' O
' O

Politics B-ORG
of I-ORG
Edinburgh I-ORG

Korea B-ORG
University I-ORG
Sejong I-ORG
Campus I-ORG
is O
a O
campus O
mainly O
in O
Sejong B-LOC
. O

F-80 B-ORG
Shooting I-ORG
Star I-ORG
( O
1950–1953 O
) O

`` O
- O
John B-PER
Doyle I-PER
, O
The B-ORG
Globe I-ORG
and I-ORG
Mail I-ORG
'' O

Juventudes B-ORG
de I-ORG
Acción I-ORG
Popular I-ORG

Zeitschrift B-ORG
für I-ORG
Instrumentenbau I-ORG

Boavista B-ORG
and O
Gondomar B-ORG
were O
relegated O
to O
Second B-ORG
Division I-ORG
. O

`` O
Flaunt B-ORG
It I-ORG
'' O
– O
TV B-ORG
Rock I-ORG
featuring O
Seany B-PER
B I-PER
( O
4 O
weeks O
) O

*Label O
: O
EMI B-ORG
( O
) O

'' O
The B-ORG
Law I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ueki I-ORG
'' O
( O
2005 O
) O
( O
Mūnin O
) O

It O
was O
written O
by O
B. B-PER
J. I-PER
Novak I-PER
and O
directed O
by O
Dennie B-PER
Gordon I-PER
and O
first O
aired O
on O
February O
2 O
, O
2006 O
on O
NBC B-ORG
. O

Der B-ORG
Emes I-ORG
( O
1918-1939 O
) O

Bridgeport B-ORG
Vasco I-ORG
da I-ORG
Gama I-ORG
, O
Bridgeport B-LOC
, I-LOC
Connecticut I-LOC
; O
United B-LOC
States I-LOC

*Museum O
Zoologi O
Ragunan B-ORG
Zoo I-ORG
, O
Jakarta B-LOC

Museo B-ORG
del I-ORG
Prado I-ORG

Hrimthursum B-ORG
'' O
- O
( O
2006 O
) O

To O
Boston B-ORG
Bruins I-ORG
Michael B-PER
Nylander I-PER

Mad B-ORG
at I-ORG
the I-ORG
World I-ORG
( I-ORG
album I-ORG
) I-ORG

He O
was O
educated O
at O
St. B-ORG
Ronan I-ORG
's I-ORG
School I-ORG
, O
Hawkhurst B-LOC
, O
Winchester B-ORG
College I-ORG
and O
Magdalen B-ORG
College I-ORG
, I-ORG
Oxford I-ORG
, O
graduating O
in O
1952 O
. O

The B-ORG
Westmeath I-ORG
Examiner I-ORG
'' O

Bushehr B-ORG
Nuclear I-ORG
Power I-ORG
Plant I-ORG

Date B-ORG
A I-ORG
Live I-ORG
'' O
( O
Tohka O
Yatogami O
) O

1925 B-ORG
Chicago I-ORG
Cardinals I-ORG
– I-ORG
Milwaukee I-ORG
Badgers I-ORG
scandal I-ORG

Santa B-ORG
Lucia I-ORG
in I-ORG
Selci I-ORG

Yo B-ORG
amo I-ORG
a I-ORG
Juan I-ORG
Querendón I-ORG
'' O
( O
starring O
Mayrín B-PER
Villanueva I-PER
and O
Eduardo B-PER
Santamarina I-PER
) O
( O
October O
12 O
, O
2015 O
– O
present O
) O

Belfast B-ORG
Metropolitan I-ORG
College I-ORG

AT B-ORG
& I-ORG
T I-ORG
Team I-ORG
USA I-ORG
Soundtrack I-ORG
( I-ORG
2010 I-ORG
) I-ORG

Star B-ORG
Trek I-ORG
: I-ORG
Deep I-ORG
Space I-ORG
Nine I-ORG
'' O

`` O
Killing B-ORG
In I-ORG
The I-ORG
Name I-ORG
'' O

=== O
National B-ORG
People I-ORG
's I-ORG
Army I-ORG
=== O

Flora B-ORG
won O
their O
second O
title O
. O

Stony B-ORG
Brook I-ORG
Seawolves I-ORG
football I-ORG

The B-ORG
Slim I-ORG
Shady I-ORG
EP I-ORG
'' O

Booker B-ORG
T I-ORG
& I-ORG
The I-ORG
MGs I-ORG

However O
, O
these O
three O
songs O
are O
available O
with O
an O
average O
quality O
on O
YouTube B-ORG
. O

' O
'' O
1997 B-ORG
'' O
' O
: O
Lisbon B-LOC
, O
Portugal B-LOC

Kildeer B-LOC
, I-LOC
Illinois I-LOC
, O
USA B-ORG

John B-PER
Coape I-PER
Sherbrooke I-PER
, O
Governor-general B-ORG
of O
British B-LOC
North I-LOC
America I-LOC

Let B-ORG
Me I-ORG
Be I-ORG
Good I-ORG
to I-ORG
You I-ORG
'' O

A1 B-ORG
Ethniki I-ORG
Women I-ORG
's I-ORG
Water I-ORG
Polo I-ORG

** O
Seattle B-ORG
Seahawks I-ORG
34 O
, O
San B-ORG
Francisco I-ORG
49ers I-ORG
13 O

He O
was O
elected O
to O
the O
Canadian B-ORG
House I-ORG
of I-ORG
Commons I-ORG
in O
1940 B-ORG
as O
a O
Member O
of O
the O
Progressive B-ORG
Conservative I-ORG
Party I-ORG
to O
represent O
the O
riding B-LOC
of O
Saskatoon B-LOC
City I-LOC
. O

*1967 O
: O
honorary O
Doctor B-ORG
of I-ORG
Laws I-ORG
from O
the O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Manitoba I-ORG

Immortal B-ORG
Admiral I-ORG
Yi I-ORG
Sun-sin I-ORG
, O
Precious B-ORG
Family I-ORG
'' O

Encounters B-ORG
'' O
( O
2000 O
) O

Jor B-ORG
Bagh I-ORG
metro I-ORG
station I-ORG

The O
Hebrew B-ORG
inscriptions O
found O
on O
Hasmonean B-ORG
coins O
are O
: O

Hélène B-PER
Joy I-PER
, O
Murdoch B-ORG
Mysteries I-ORG
'' O

Later O
, O
on O
19 O
November O
2011 O
, O
they O
performed O
the O
song O
on O
Saturday B-ORG
Night I-ORG
Live I-ORG
'' O
. O

Sinclair B-ORG
Community I-ORG
College I-ORG
- O
Dayton B-LOC

According O
to O
the O
2001 B-ORG
Ukrainian I-ORG
Census I-ORG
: O

`` O
So B-ORG
Gently I-ORG
We I-ORG
Go I-ORG
'' O

St. B-ORG
Luke I-ORG
's I-ORG
Orthodox I-ORG
Cathedral I-ORG

: O
Headquarters O
, O
Thirteenth B-ORG
Air I-ORG
Force I-ORG
, O
13–21 O
January O
1943 O

List B-ORG
of I-ORG
notable I-ORG
tropical I-ORG
cyclones I-ORG

Bishop B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bath I-ORG
and I-ORG
Wells I-ORG

Derek B-ORG
( I-ORG
TV I-ORG
series I-ORG
) I-ORG

Polish–Swedish B-ORG
War I-ORG
( I-ORG
1617–18 I-ORG
) I-ORG

Light B-ORG
Blue I-ORG
Line I-ORG
( I-ORG
Bangkok I-ORG
Rapid I-ORG
Transit I-ORG
) I-ORG

*20px O
Florida B-ORG
State I-ORG
Road I-ORG
93 I-ORG

Fair B-ORG
Labor I-ORG
Standards I-ORG
Act I-ORG
of I-ORG
1938 I-ORG

** O
Built O
by O
: O
Deptford B-ORG
Dockyard I-ORG
. O

Xinjiang B-ORG
Production I-ORG
and I-ORG
Construction I-ORG
Corps I-ORG

Illinois B-ORG
Route I-ORG
120 I-ORG

You B-ORG
Do I-ORG
n't I-ORG
Care I-ORG
About I-ORG
Us I-ORG

Split O
with O
: O
NORA B-ORG

Fresh B-ORG
Sounds I-ORG
From I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
America I-ORG
( I-ORG
vol I-ORG
5 I-ORG
) I-ORG

Crazy B-ORG
: I-ORG
The I-ORG
Demo I-ORG
Sessions I-ORG
'' O

Some B-ORG
Friendly I-ORG
– I-ORG
20th I-ORG
Anniversary I-ORG
Concerts I-ORG

Ben B-PER
Folds I-PER
( O
Ben B-ORG
Folds I-ORG
Five I-ORG
) O

*60px O
Joint B-ORG
Service I-ORG
Commendation I-ORG
Medal I-ORG

Manu B-ORG
Ginobili I-ORG
( O
23 O
) O

Francesco B-PER
Botticini I-PER
or O
Andrea B-ORG
Castagna I-ORG

He O
was O
drafted O
in O
the O
fifth O
round O
of O
the O
2007 B-ORG
NFL I-ORG
Draft I-ORG
by O
the O
New B-ORG
York I-ORG
Giants I-ORG
out O
of O
Western B-ORG
Oregon I-ORG
University I-ORG
. O

Paul B-PER
Beesley I-PER
- O
Sheffield B-ORG
United I-ORG
, O
2 O
August O
1995 O
, O
£250,000 O

It O
is O
used O
by O
the O
United B-ORG
States I-ORG
Marine I-ORG
Corps I-ORG
. O

CTT B-ORG
( I-ORG
Macau I-ORG
) I-ORG

' O
'' O
Analogue B-ORG
Bubblebath I-ORG
4 I-ORG
'' O
' O
'' O

Stacy B-PER
London I-PER
( O
Fashion B-ORG
stylist I-ORG
from O
What B-ORG
Not I-ORG
to I-ORG
Wear I-ORG
'' O
) O

Estadio B-ORG
Regional I-ORG
de I-ORG
Antofagasta I-ORG
, O
Antofagasta B-LOC

American B-ORG
Music I-ORG
Awards I-ORG
of I-ORG
1980 I-ORG

2,000 B-ORG
Guineas I-ORG
Stakes I-ORG
– O
El B-LOC
Gran I-LOC
Senor I-LOC

' O
'' O
892 B-ORG
in I-ORG
poetry I-ORG
'' O
' O

at O
Birmingham-Southern B-ORG
College I-ORG
in O
1965 O
. O

Hindus B-ORG
practice O
a O
variety O
of O
rituals O
from O
birth O
to O
death O
. O

*** O
Al B-ORG
Rayyan I-ORG
86 O
, O
Astana B-ORG
Tigers I-ORG
75 O

`` O
Birth B-ORG
Of I-ORG
The I-ORG
Boogie I-ORG
'' O
– O
No O
. O

Newsletter B-ORG
for I-ORG
Birdwatchers I-ORG
'' O
29 O
( O
7–8 O
) O
:7 O
. O

Songs B-ORG
from I-ORG
the I-ORG
Movies I-ORG
and I-ORG
More I-ORG
'' O

1997 O
, O
1998 O
, O
2002 O
, O
2008 O
Detroit B-ORG
Red I-ORG
Wings I-ORG

Confluent B-ORG
hypergeometric I-ORG
function I-ORG

Breed B-ORG
Groups I-ORG
( I-ORG
dog I-ORG
) I-ORG

Lieutenant B-ORG
Governor I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
Brunswick I-ORG
– O
Herménégilde B-PER
Chiasson I-PER
( O
until O
September O
30 O
) O
then O
Graydon B-PER
Nicholas I-PER

Minnesota B-ORG
Timberwolves I-ORG
( O
4 O
) O

'' O
United B-ORG
Counties I-ORG
League I-ORG
'' O
' O

U.S. B-ORG
Route I-ORG
41 I-ORG
in I-ORG
Illinois I-ORG

With O
the O
success O
of O
the O
single B-ORG
'Vendaval O
' O
in O
Belém B-LOC
, O
the O
band O
's O
songs O
became O
known O
throughout O
the O
Northeast O
. O

' O
'' O
EGOQ O
'' O
' O
– O
RAF B-ORG
Mona I-ORG
– O
Anglesey B-LOC
, O
Wales B-LOC

Udinese B-ORG
1–2 O
( O
0–1 O
) O
' O
'' O
Arsenal B-ORG
'' O
' O
. O

He O
joined O
Boreham B-ORG
Wood I-ORG
on O
15 O
February O
2013 O
. O

Edgewood B-ORG
College I-ORG
( O
Madison B-LOC
, I-LOC
Wisconsin I-LOC
) O
Official O
site O

Free B-ORG
Radio I-ORG
'' O
( O
VH1 B-ORG
) O

It O
took O
place O
at O
the O
Taube B-ORG
Tennis I-ORG
Center I-ORG
in O
Stanford B-LOC
, I-LOC
California I-LOC
, O
United B-LOC
States I-LOC
, O
from O
July O
23 O
through O
July O
29 O
, O
2007 O
. O

** O
'' O
County B-ORG
of I-ORG
Vermandois I-ORG
'' O
' O
– O
Herbert B-PER
I I-PER
( O
896–907 O
) O

'' O
Stan B-ORG
, O
'' O
Eminem B-PER

Kentish B-ORG
Town I-ORG
West I-ORG
railway I-ORG
station I-ORG

: O
*An O
abbreviated O
( O
2:48 O
) O
version O
of O
this O
mix O
appears O
on O
Disco B-ORG
2 I-ORG
'' O

`` O
– O
The B-ORG
Guardian I-ORG
'' O

The B-ORG
Next I-ORG
: I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
Is I-ORG
at I-ORG
Your I-ORG
Doorstep I-ORG
'' O

Ciudad B-ORG
de I-ORG
Guatemala I-ORG
, O
Guatemala B-LOC

2011–12 B-ORG
Brisbane I-ORG
Bandits I-ORG
season I-ORG

Lake B-ORG
Katharine I-ORG
State I-ORG
Nature I-ORG
Preserve I-ORG
in O
Jackson B-LOC
County I-LOC
, I-LOC
Ohio I-LOC

Navarra B-ORG
Foral I-ORG
Alliance I-ORG

Survivor B-ORG
Philippines I-ORG
: I-ORG
Celebrity I-ORG
Showdown I-ORG
Live I-ORG
Finale I-ORG
'' O
( O
December O
3 O
, O
2010 O
) O

*Chapter O
309 O
: O
Boy B-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
America I-ORG

It O
is O
operated O
by O
the O
United B-ORG
States I-ORG
Department I-ORG
of I-ORG
Veterans I-ORG
Affairs I-ORG
. O

Stade B-ORG
de I-ORG
Gerland I-ORG
, O
Lyon B-LOC
( O
A O
) O

Chang–Everton B-ORG
Football I-ORG
Academy I-ORG

Dry B-ORG
As I-ORG
a I-ORG
Bone I-ORG
/ I-ORG
Rehab I-ORG
Doll I-ORG
'' O

**The O
Franco-Syrian B-ORG
Treaty I-ORG
of I-ORG
Independence I-ORG
is O
signed O
. O

Dao B-ORG
Heng I-ORG
Bank I-ORG

' O
'' O
Atlético B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
'' O
' O

The O
fourth O
track O
on O
the O
album O
`` O
Back O
In O
Time O
'' O
was O
covered O
by O
Angel B-ORG
City I-ORG
( I-ORG
electronic I-ORG
music I-ORG
group I-ORG
) I-ORG
for O
their O
album O
Love B-ORG
Me I-ORG
Right I-ORG
in O
2005 O
. O

Playaz B-ORG
Circle I-ORG
- O
`` O
What O
Up O
'' O

*The O
German B-ORG
federal I-ORG
election I-ORG
was O
held O
. O

Crossland B-ORG
Construction I-ORG
Company I-ORG

: O
2004 B-ORG
– O
withdrew O
in O
First O
Round O

2013 B-ORG
Lahad I-ORG
Datu I-ORG
standoff I-ORG

Sonic B-ORG
the I-ORG
Hedgehog I-ORG
'' O
68 O
( O
1999 O
) O

Jail B-ORG
( I-ORG
TV I-ORG
series I-ORG
) I-ORG

Guangdong B-ORG
Sunray I-ORG
Cave I-ORG
F.C I-ORG
. I-ORG

' O
'' O
Grinspoon B-ORG
'' O
' O

He O
was O
part O
of O
the O
Canada B-ORG
men I-ORG
's I-ORG
national I-ORG
volleyball I-ORG
team I-ORG
. O

Monument B-ORG
of I-ORG
Culture I-ORG
of I-ORG
Exceptional I-ORG
Importance I-ORG

*1955 O
: O
Gösta B-PER
Hammarlund I-PER
, O
Dagbladet B-ORG
'' O

CST B-ORG
Brands I-ORG
, I-ORG
Inc I-ORG
. I-ORG

It O
host O
the O
tennis B-ORG
event I-ORG
at O
the O
2010 B-PER
Asian I-PER
Games I-PER
. O

On O
21 O
December O
1934 O
, O
he O
joined O
the O
Ustaše B-ORG
in O
Italy B-LOC
. O

The O
Communist B-ORG
International I-ORG
was O
established O
at O
the O
Founding B-LOC
Congress I-LOC
held O
in O
Moscow B-LOC
in O
March O
1919 O
. O

: O
''See O
FirstMerit B-ORG
Tower I-ORG
for O
more O
information O
. O

Pearl B-ORG
Jam I-ORG
held O
a O
concert O
on O
26 O
September O
2006 O
. O

Charles B-ORG
Philip I-ORG
Haddon-Cave I-ORG
, O
former O
Financial B-ORG
Secretary I-ORG
of O
Hong B-LOC
Kong I-LOC

Torneo B-ORG
Descentralizado I-ORG
( O
3 O
) O
: O
2007 B-LOC
, O
2008 B-LOC
, O
2010 B-LOC

Included O
on O
1979 O
album O
Quiet B-ORG
Life I-ORG
'' O
( O
– O
4:53 O
) O
. O

*** O
by B-ORG
GDP I-ORG
per I-ORG
capita I-ORG

Victoria B-ORG
College I-ORG
, I-ORG
Jersey I-ORG

`` O
Blue B-ORG
in I-ORG
Green I-ORG
'' O
( O
Miles B-PER
Davis I-PER
) O
-- O
2:38 O

He O
has O
hosted O
a O
number O
of O
shows O
on O
WXST B-ORG
, O
WJIM B-ORG
and O
was O
the O
co-host O
of O
`` O
Back O
to O
Back O
'' O
on O
WTVS B-ORG
. O

Ponca B-ORG
City I-ORG
, O
Oklahoma B-LOC
, O
United B-LOC
States I-LOC

Les B-ORG
Mots I-ORG
( I-ORG
album I-ORG
) I-ORG

Tracks O
12 O
, O
14 O
and O
15 O
were O
reprised O
and O
appeared O
on O
Direction B-ORG
of I-ORG
Things I-ORG
to I-ORG
Come I-ORG
'' O
in O
November O
, O
1997 O

'' O
Hypernauts B-ORG
'' O
( O
1996 O
) O

JR2F B-ORG
Albatross I-ORG
- O
Grumman B-ORG

: O
This O
song O
was O
covered O
by O
Pro-Pain B-ORG
for O
their O
album O
`` O
Run O
For O
Cover O
'' O
. O

Harrah B-ORG
's I-ORG
Entertainment I-ORG
– O
William B-PER
F. I-PER
Harrah I-PER

Hugh B-ORG
Ewing I-ORG
and O
George B-PER
Crook I-PER
) O
. O

Madison B-ORG
Township I-ORG
, O
Lac B-LOC
qui I-LOC
Parle I-LOC
County I-LOC

The O
five O
top-tier O
sponsors O
were O
Coca-Cola B-ORG
, O
Adidas B-ORG
, O
Hyundai–Kia B-ORG
, O
Visa B-ORG
, O
and O
Gazprom B-ORG
. O

Didcot B-ORG
Parkway I-ORG
railway I-ORG
station I-ORG

Romanza B-ORG
by O
Andrea B-PER
Bocelli I-PER

They O
compete O
under O
the O
auspice O
of O
the O
Collegiate B-ORG
Water I-ORG
Polo I-ORG
Association I-ORG
. O

European B-ORG
Cup I-ORG
Winners I-ORG
' I-ORG
Cup I-ORG
1996 I-ORG

Stockholms B-ORG
län I-ORG
, O
seat O
no O
. O

List B-ORG
of I-ORG
top I-ORG
English I-ORG
points I-ORG
scorers I-ORG
and I-ORG
try I-ORG
scorers I-ORG

The O
song O
debuted O
on O
American B-ORG
Idol I-ORG
'' O
on O
May O
6 O
, O
2009 O
. O

'' O
The B-ORG
Magic I-ORG
Lie I-ORG
'' O
( O
1977-1979 O
) O

Indian B-ORG
Movement I-ORG
Túpac I-ORG
Katari-One I-ORG

** O
'' O
Duchy B-ORG
of I-ORG
Pomerania I-ORG
'' O
' O
– O
Bogislaw B-PER
X I-PER
( O
1478–1523 O
) O

They O
finished O
in O
second O
place O
in O
the O
American B-ORG
League I-ORG
East I-ORG
with O
an O
84-78 O
record O
, O
which O
was O
their O
worst O
since O
1992 B-ORG
. O

'' O
30 B-ORG
Rock I-ORG
'' O

''Des B-ORG
Moines I-ORG
'' I-ORG
( I-ORG
C-15 I-ORG
) I-ORG

Pacific B-ORG
Crest I-ORG
National I-ORG
Scenic I-ORG
Trail I-ORG

Beside B-ORG
You I-ORG
in I-ORG
Time I-ORG

Baku B-ORG
World I-ORG
Challenge I-ORG
, O
Baku B-LOC

Horse B-ORG
Guards I-ORG
in O
London B-LOC
, O
designed O
by O
William B-PER
Kent I-PER
and O
John B-PER
Vardy I-PER
, O
is O
completed O
. O

Office B-ORG
97 I-ORG
Small I-ORG
Business I-ORG
Edition I-ORG
SR2 I-ORG

Premier B-ORG
League I-ORG
( O
1 O
) O
: O
1998–99 B-LOC

Currently O
lease O
from O
Sky B-ORG
Wings I-ORG
Asia I-ORG
Airlines I-ORG
- O
XU-ZAB O
. O

Lieutenant B-ORG
Governor I-ORG
of I-ORG
Saskatchewan I-ORG
– O
Frederick B-PER
Johnson I-PER

The B-ORG
Ski I-ORG
Channel I-ORG

It O
was O
intended O
for O
the O
Smile B-ORG
'' O
album O
until O
the O
project O
was O
shelved O
. O

David B-PER
Gilmour I-PER
also O
recorded O
a O
version O
on O
his O
solo B-ORG
debut I-ORG
album I-ORG
. O

Siege B-ORG
of I-ORG
Cambrai I-ORG
( I-ORG
1677 I-ORG
) I-ORG

Reference B-ORG
re I-ORG
Firearms I-ORG
Act I-ORG
'' O

He O
was O
born O
at O
East B-ORG
Dereham I-ORG
, O
Norfolk B-LOC
and O
died O
at O
Dartford B-LOC
, O
Kent B-LOC
. O

3rd B-ORG
Eye I-ORG
Vision I-ORG
'' O
( O
1998 O
) O

1968 O
- O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Dortmund I-ORG
established O
. O

Deel B-ORG
( I-ORG
disambiguation I-ORG
) I-ORG
